{"title":"When Love Comes Along","plot":"Between getting trashed, tripping, blowing guys off and writing songs, Mark falls for Stephen. Fig and Sally put perform Marks songs between casual sex with anyone and everyone. Katie is a few-hit wonder who hit rock-bottom in L.A and returns to New Zealand to patch her life back together. Stephen, Mark and Katie branch out for a slumber party at a beach house of their better days. Fig and Sally arrive, and not long after Eddie arrives also (Katies American guy). Mark stops running away from Stephens love, Katie and Eddie get engaged and Fig and Sally ... have sex?","genres":["Drama"," Romance"],"stems":["Between","get","trash",",","trip",",","blow","guy","off","and","write","song",",","Mark","fall","for","Stephen",".","Fig","and","Salli","put","perform","Mark","song","between","casual","sex","with","anyon","and","everyon",".","Kati","is","a","few-hit","wonder","who","hit","rock-bottom","in","L.A","and","return","to","New","Zealand","to","patch","her","life","back","togeth",".","Stephen",",","Mark","and","Kati","branch","out","for","a","slumber","parti","at","a","beach","hous","of","their","better","day",".","Fig","and","Salli","arriv",",","and","not","long","after","Eddie","arriv","also","(","Kati","American","guy",")",".","Mark","stop","run","away","from","Stephen","love",",","Kati","and","Eddie","get","engag","and","Fig","and","Salli","...","have","sex","?"],"lemmas":["between","get","trash",",","trip",",","blow","guy","off","and","write","song",",","Mark","fall","for","Stephen",".","Fig","and","Sally","put","perform","Marks","song","between","casual","sex","with","anyone","and","everyone",".","Katie","be","a","few-hit","wonder","who","hit","rock-bottom","in","L.A","and","return","to","New","Zealand","to","patch","she","life","back","together",".","Stephen",",","Mark","and","Katie","branch","out","for","a","slumber","party","at","a","beach","house","of","they","better","day",".","Fig","and","Sally","arrive",",","and","not","long","after","Eddie","arrive","also","-lrb-","Katies","American","guy","-rrb-",".","Mark","stop","run","away","from","Stephens","love",",","Katie","and","Eddie","get","engage","and","Fig","and","Sally","...","have","sex","?"],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","ORGANIZATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Between getting trashed","getting trashed ,","trashed , tripping",", tripping ,","tripping , blowing",", blowing guys","blowing guys off","guys off and","off and writing","and writing songs","writing songs ,","songs , Mark",", Mark falls","Mark falls for","falls for Stephen","Fig and Sally","and Sally put","Sally put perform","put perform Marks","perform Marks songs","Marks songs between","songs between casual","between casual sex","casual sex with","sex with anyone","with anyone and","anyone and everyone","Katie is a","is a few-hit","a few-hit wonder","few-hit wonder who","wonder who hit","who hit rock-bottom","hit rock-bottom in","rock-bottom in L.A","in L.A and","L.A and returns","and returns to","returns to New","to New Zealand","New Zealand to","Zealand to patch","to patch her","patch her life","her life back","life back together","Stephen , Mark",", Mark and","Mark and Katie","and Katie branch","Katie branch out","branch out for","out for a","for a slumber","a slumber party","slumber party at","party at a","at a beach","a beach house","beach house of","house of their","of their better","their better days","Fig and Sally","and Sally arrive","Sally arrive ,","arrive , and",", and not","and not long","not long after","long after Eddie","after Eddie arrives","Eddie arrives also","arrives also (","also ( Katies","( Katies American","Katies American guy","American guy )","Mark stops running","stops running away","running away from","away from Stephens","from Stephens love","Stephens love ,","love , Katie",", Katie and","Katie and Eddie","and Eddie get","Eddie get engaged","get engaged and","engaged and Fig","and Fig and","Fig and Sally","and Sally ...","Sally ... have","... have sex"],"2grams":["Between getting","getting trashed","trashed ,",", tripping","tripping ,",", blowing","blowing guys","guys off","off and","and writing","writing songs","songs ,",", Mark","Mark falls","falls for","for Stephen","Fig and","and Sally","Sally put","put perform","perform Marks","Marks songs","songs between","between casual","casual sex","sex with","with anyone","anyone and","and everyone","Katie is","is a","a few-hit","few-hit wonder","wonder who","who hit","hit rock-bottom","rock-bottom in","in L.A","L.A and","and returns","returns to","to New","New Zealand","Zealand to","to patch","patch her","her life","life back","back together","Stephen ,",", Mark","Mark and","and Katie","Katie branch","branch out","out for","for a","a slumber","slumber party","party at","at a","a beach","beach house","house of","of their","their better","better days","Fig and","and Sally","Sally arrive","arrive ,",", and","and not","not long","long after","after Eddie","Eddie arrives","arrives also","also (","( Katies","Katies American","American guy","guy )","Mark stops","stops running","running away","away from","from Stephens","Stephens love","love ,",", Katie","Katie and","and Eddie","Eddie get","get engaged","engaged and","and Fig","Fig and","and Sally","Sally ...","... have","have sex"]}