{"title":"White Lies","plot":"Jeanne is a young weirdo girl who flies to Paris, and is hired by an old lady called Madeleine as an au pair. Jeanne lies to Madeleine, she says she comes from a very rich family. Young Madeleine's admirer Antoine and another thug, Marcel, kidnap Jeanne when they hear she's a millionaire. But the problem is that Jeanne's parents are poor and Antoine soon falls for her.","genres":["Comedy"," Crime"],"stems":["Jeann","is","a","young","weirdo","girl","who","fli","to","Pari",",","and","is","hire","by","an","old","ladi","call","Madelein","as","an","au","pair",".","Jeann","lie","to","Madelein",",","she","say","she","come","from","a","veri","rich","famili",".","Young","Madelein","'s","admir","Antoin","and","anoth","thug",",","Marcel",",","kidnap","Jeann","when","they","hear","she","'s","a","millionair",".","But","the","problem","is","that","Jeann","'s","parent","are","poor","and","Antoin","soon","fall","for","her","."],"lemmas":["Jeanne","be","a","young","weirdo","girl","who","fly","to","Paris",",","and","be","hire","by","a","old","lady","call","Madeleine","as","a","au","pair",".","Jeanne","lie","to","Madeleine",",","she","say","she","come","from","a","very","rich","family",".","Young","Madeleine","'s","admirer","Antoine","and","another","thug",",","Marcel",",","kidnap","Jeanne","when","they","hear","she","be","a","millionaire",".","but","the","problem","be","that","Jeanne","'s","parent","be","poor","and","Antoine","soon","fall","for","she","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Jeanne is a","is a young","a young weirdo","young weirdo girl","weirdo girl who","girl who flies","who flies to","flies to Paris","to Paris ,","Paris , and",", and is","and is hired","is hired by","hired by an","by an old","an old lady","old lady called","lady called Madeleine","called Madeleine as","Madeleine as an","as an au","an au pair","Jeanne lies to","lies to Madeleine","to Madeleine ,","Madeleine , she",", she says","she says she","says she comes","she comes from","comes from a","from a very","a very rich","very rich family","Young Madeleine 's","Madeleine 's admirer","'s admirer Antoine","admirer Antoine and","Antoine and another","and another thug","another thug ,","thug , Marcel",", Marcel ,","Marcel , kidnap",", kidnap Jeanne","kidnap Jeanne when","Jeanne when they","when they hear","they hear she","hear she 's","she 's a","'s a millionaire","But the problem","the problem is","problem is that","is that Jeanne","that Jeanne 's","Jeanne 's parents","'s parents are","parents are poor","are poor and","poor and Antoine","and Antoine soon","Antoine soon falls","soon falls for","falls for her"],"2grams":["Jeanne is","is a","a young","young weirdo","weirdo girl","girl who","who flies","flies to","to Paris","Paris ,",", and","and is","is hired","hired by","by an","an old","old lady","lady called","called Madeleine","Madeleine as","as an","an au","au pair","Jeanne lies","lies to","to Madeleine","Madeleine ,",", she","she says","says she","she comes","comes from","from a","a very","very rich","rich family","Young Madeleine","Madeleine 's","'s admirer","admirer Antoine","Antoine and","and another","another thug","thug ,",", Marcel","Marcel ,",", kidnap","kidnap Jeanne","Jeanne when","when they","they hear","hear she","she 's","'s a","a millionaire","But the","the problem","problem is","is that","that Jeanne","Jeanne 's","'s parents","parents are","are poor","poor and","and Antoine","Antoine soon","soon falls","falls for","for her"]}