{"title":"Looking for Leonard","plot":"Ted, his girlfriend Jo, and his brother Johnny are small-time robbers in Montreal. The brothers spend their time watching TV, while Jo rereads Leonard Cohen's novel \"Beautiful Losers\" and attends writing classes. Luka, a Czech immigrant, picks up Jo when he sees her shoplifting. When Johnny surprises Luka kissing Jo, he attacks him. In the ensuing fight Jo accidentally kills Johnny, and Luka leaves the scene, but drops his wallet. The police assume that Luka attacked Johnny after a break-in and Jo goes along with that, but feels guilty about it.","genres":["Comedy"," Drama"," Crime"],"stems":["Ted",",","his","girlfriend","Jo",",","and","his","brother","Johnni","are","small-tim","robber","in","Montreal",".","The","brother","spend","their","time","watch","TV",",","while","Jo","reread","Leonard","Cohen","'s","novel","\"","Beauti","Loser","\"","and","attend","write","class",".","Luka",",","a","Czech","immigr",",","pick","up","Jo","when","he","see","her","shoplift",".","When","Johnni","surpris","Luka","kiss","Jo",",","he","attack","him",".","In","the","ensu","fight","Jo","accident","kill","Johnni",",","and","Luka","leav","the","scene",",","but","drop","his","wallet",".","The","polic","assum","that","Luka","attack","Johnni","after","a","break-in","and","Jo","goe","along","with","that",",","but","feel","guilti","about","it","."],"lemmas":["Ted",",","he","girlfriend","Jo",",","and","he","brother","Johnny","be","small-time","robber","in","Montreal",".","the","brother","spend","they","time","watch","tv",",","while","Jo","reread","Leonard","Cohen","'s","novel","``","beautiful","loser","''","and","attend","write","class",".","Luka",",","a","czech","immigrant",",","pick","up","Jo","when","he","see","she","shoplifting",".","when","Johnny","surprise","Luka","kiss","Jo",",","he","attack","he",".","in","the","ensue","fight","Jo","accidentally","kill","Johnny",",","and","Luka","leave","the","scene",",","but","drop","he","wallet",".","the","police","assume","that","Luka","attack","Johnny","after","a","break-in","and","Jo","go","along","with","that",",","but","feel","guilty","about","it","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Ted , his",", his girlfriend","his girlfriend Jo","girlfriend Jo ,","Jo , and",", and his","and his brother","his brother Johnny","brother Johnny are","Johnny are small-time","are small-time robbers","small-time robbers in","robbers in Montreal","The brothers spend","brothers spend their","spend their time","their time watching","time watching TV","watching TV ,","TV , while",", while Jo","while Jo rereads","Jo rereads Leonard","rereads Leonard Cohen","Leonard Cohen 's","Cohen 's novel","'s novel \"","novel \" Beautiful","\" Beautiful Losers","Beautiful Losers \"","Losers \" and","\" and attends","and attends writing","attends writing classes","Luka , a",", a Czech","a Czech immigrant","Czech immigrant ,","immigrant , picks",", picks up","picks up Jo","up Jo when","Jo when he","when he sees","he sees her","sees her shoplifting","When Johnny surprises","Johnny surprises Luka","surprises Luka kissing","Luka kissing Jo","kissing Jo ,","Jo , he",", he attacks","he attacks him","In the ensuing","the ensuing fight","ensuing fight Jo","fight Jo accidentally","Jo accidentally kills","accidentally kills Johnny","kills Johnny ,","Johnny , and",", and Luka","and Luka leaves","Luka leaves the","leaves the scene","the scene ,","scene , but",", but drops","but drops his","drops his wallet","The police assume","police assume that","assume that Luka","that Luka attacked","Luka attacked Johnny","attacked Johnny after","Johnny after a","after a break-in","a break-in and","break-in and Jo","and Jo goes","Jo goes along","goes along with","along with that","with that ,","that , but",", but feels","but feels guilty","feels guilty about","guilty about it"],"2grams":["Ted ,",", his","his girlfriend","girlfriend Jo","Jo ,",", and","and his","his brother","brother Johnny","Johnny are","are small-time","small-time robbers","robbers in","in Montreal","The brothers","brothers spend","spend their","their time","time watching","watching TV","TV ,",", while","while Jo","Jo rereads","rereads Leonard","Leonard Cohen","Cohen 's","'s novel","novel \"","\" Beautiful","Beautiful Losers","Losers \"","\" and","and attends","attends writing","writing classes","Luka ,",", a","a Czech","Czech immigrant","immigrant ,",", picks","picks up","up Jo","Jo when","when he","he sees","sees her","her shoplifting","When Johnny","Johnny surprises","surprises Luka","Luka kissing","kissing Jo","Jo ,",", he","he attacks","attacks him","In the","the ensuing","ensuing fight","fight Jo","Jo accidentally","accidentally kills","kills Johnny","Johnny ,",", and","and Luka","Luka leaves","leaves the","the scene","scene ,",", but","but drops","drops his","his wallet","The police","police assume","assume that","that Luka","Luka attacked","attacked Johnny","Johnny after","after a","a break-in","break-in and","and Jo","Jo goes","goes along","along with","with that","that ,",", but","but feels","feels guilty","guilty about","about it"]}