{"title":"Shotgun Freeway: Drives Through Lost L.A.","plot":"A political and social history of Los Angeles, using old stills and news footage, contemporary footage, and commentary. Bert Corona is our guide for East Los Angeles, Buck Henry for Hollywood, David Hockney for the art scene, Elaine Young for Beverly Hills, Buddy Collette and Gene Norman for Central Avenue and music, Margaret Crawford and Joan Didion for the San Fernando Valley, James Ellroy for noir L.A., Frank Wilkinson on land use and L.A.'s poor, and, throughout, the observations of Mike Davis, L.A.'s pre-eminent social historian.","genres":["Documentary"],"stems":["A","polit","and","social","histori","of","Los","Angele",",","use","old","still","and","news","footag",",","contemporari","footag",",","and","commentari",".","Bert","Corona","is","our","guid","for","East","Los","Angele",",","Buck","Henri","for","Hollywood",",","David","Hockney","for","the","art","scene",",","Elain","Young","for","Bever","Hill",",","Buddi","Collett","and","Gene","Norman","for","Central","Avenu","and","music",",","Margaret","Crawford","and","Joan","Didion","for","the","San","Fernando","Valley",",","Jame","Ellroy","for","noir","L.A.",",","Frank","Wilkinson","on","land","use","and","L.A.","'s","poor",",","and",",","throughout",",","the","observ","of","Mike","Davi",",","L.A.","'s","pre-emin","social","historian","."],"lemmas":["a","political","and","social","history","of","Los","Angeles",",","use","old","still","and","news","footage",",","contemporary","footage",",","and","commentary",".","Bert","Corona","be","we","guide","for","East","Los","Angeles",",","Buck","Henry","for","Hollywood",",","David","Hockney","for","the","art","scene",",","Elaine","Young","for","Beverly","Hills",",","Buddy","Collette","and","Gene","Norman","for","Central","Avenue","and","music",",","Margaret","Crawford","and","Joan","Didion","for","the","San","Fernando","Valley",",","James","Ellroy","for","noir","L.A.",",","Frank","Wilkinson","on","land","use","and","L.A.","'s","poor",",","and",",","throughout",",","the","observation","of","Mike","Davis",",","L.A.","'s","pre-eminent","social","historian","."],"named_entities":["ORGANIZATION","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION"],"3grams":["A political and","political and social","and social history","social history of","history of Los","of Los Angeles","Los Angeles ,","Angeles , using",", using old","using old stills","old stills and","stills and news","and news footage","news footage ,","footage , contemporary",", contemporary footage","contemporary footage ,","footage , and",", and commentary","Bert Corona is","Corona is our","is our guide","our guide for","guide for East","for East Los","East Los Angeles","Los Angeles ,","Angeles , Buck",", Buck Henry","Buck Henry for","Henry for Hollywood","for Hollywood ,","Hollywood , David",", David Hockney","David Hockney for","Hockney for the","for the art","the art scene","art scene ,","scene , Elaine",", Elaine Young","Elaine Young for","Young for Beverly","for Beverly Hills","Beverly Hills ,","Hills , Buddy",", Buddy Collette","Buddy Collette and","Collette and Gene","and Gene Norman","Gene Norman for","Norman for Central","for Central Avenue","Central Avenue and","Avenue and music","and music ,","music , Margaret",", Margaret Crawford","Margaret Crawford and","Crawford and Joan","and Joan Didion","Joan Didion for","Didion for the","for the San","the San Fernando","San Fernando Valley","Fernando Valley ,","Valley , James",", James Ellroy","James Ellroy for","Ellroy for noir","for noir L.A.","noir L.A. ,","L.A. , Frank",", Frank Wilkinson","Frank Wilkinson on","Wilkinson on land","on land use","land use and","use and L.A.","and L.A. 's","L.A. 's poor","'s poor ,","poor , and",", and ,","and , throughout",", throughout ,","throughout , the",", the observations","the observations of","observations of Mike","of Mike Davis","Mike Davis ,","Davis , L.A.",", L.A. 's","L.A. 's pre-eminent","'s pre-eminent social","pre-eminent social historian"],"2grams":["A political","political and","and social","social history","history of","of Los","Los Angeles","Angeles ,",", using","using old","old stills","stills and","and news","news footage","footage ,",", contemporary","contemporary footage","footage ,",", and","and commentary","Bert Corona","Corona is","is our","our guide","guide for","for East","East Los","Los Angeles","Angeles ,",", Buck","Buck Henry","Henry for","for Hollywood","Hollywood ,",", David","David Hockney","Hockney for","for the","the art","art scene","scene ,",", Elaine","Elaine Young","Young for","for Beverly","Beverly Hills","Hills ,",", Buddy","Buddy Collette","Collette and","and Gene","Gene Norman","Norman for","for Central","Central Avenue","Avenue and","and music","music ,",", Margaret","Margaret Crawford","Crawford and","and Joan","Joan Didion","Didion for","for the","the San","San Fernando","Fernando Valley","Valley ,",", James","James Ellroy","Ellroy for","for noir","noir L.A.","L.A. ,",", Frank","Frank Wilkinson","Wilkinson on","on land","land use","use and","and L.A.","L.A. 's","'s poor","poor ,",", and","and ,",", throughout","throughout ,",", the","the observations","observations of","of Mike","Mike Davis","Davis ,",", L.A.","L.A. 's","'s pre-eminent","pre-eminent social","social historian"]}