{"title":"Joey","plot":"Billy is a boy who is trying to save a baby kangaroo called Joey after its family is captured and taken to Sydney. Billy travels to Sydney to reunite Joey with his family only to discover that Joey is not the only one who needs to be saved. Linda, the young daughter of the U.S. Ambassador joins Billy as they fight to save Joey.","genres":["Adventure"," Family"," Comedy"],"stems":["Billi","is","a","boy","who","is","tri","to","save","a","babi","kangaroo","call","Joey","after","it","famili","is","captur","and","taken","to","Sydney",".","Billi","travel","to","Sydney","to","reunit","Joey","with","his","famili","onli","to","discov","that","Joey","is","not","the","onli","one","who","need","to","be","save",".","Linda",",","the","young","daughter","of","the","U.S.","Ambassador","join","Billi","as","they","fight","to","save","Joey","."],"lemmas":["Billy","be","a","boy","who","be","try","to","save","a","baby","kangaroo","call","Joey","after","its","family","be","capture","and","take","to","Sydney",".","Billy","travel","to","Sydney","to","reunite","Joey","with","he","family","only","to","discover","that","Joey","be","not","the","only","one","who","need","to","be","save",".","Linda",",","the","young","daughter","of","the","U.S.","Ambassador","join","Billy","as","they","fight","to","save","Joey","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Billy is a","is a boy","a boy who","boy who is","who is trying","is trying to","trying to save","to save a","save a baby","a baby kangaroo","baby kangaroo called","kangaroo called Joey","called Joey after","Joey after its","after its family","its family is","family is captured","is captured and","captured and taken","and taken to","taken to Sydney","Billy travels to","travels to Sydney","to Sydney to","Sydney to reunite","to reunite Joey","reunite Joey with","Joey with his","with his family","his family only","family only to","only to discover","to discover that","discover that Joey","that Joey is","Joey is not","is not the","not the only","the only one","only one who","one who needs","who needs to","needs to be","to be saved","Linda , the",", the young","the young daughter","young daughter of","daughter of the","of the U.S.","the U.S. Ambassador","U.S. Ambassador joins","Ambassador joins Billy","joins Billy as","Billy as they","as they fight","they fight to","fight to save","to save Joey"],"2grams":["Billy is","is a","a boy","boy who","who is","is trying","trying to","to save","save a","a baby","baby kangaroo","kangaroo called","called Joey","Joey after","after its","its family","family is","is captured","captured and","and taken","taken to","to Sydney","Billy travels","travels to","to Sydney","Sydney to","to reunite","reunite Joey","Joey with","with his","his family","family only","only to","to discover","discover that","that Joey","Joey is","is not","not the","the only","only one","one who","who needs","needs to","to be","be saved","Linda ,",", the","the young","young daughter","daughter of","of the","the U.S.","U.S. Ambassador","Ambassador joins","joins Billy","Billy as","as they","they fight","fight to","to save","save Joey"]}