{"title":"Stiff Upper Lips","plot":"Young upper-class fellow Edward arrives with his friend Cedric at the family manse, Ivory Hall. He plans to pair off Cedric with his sister Emily. Emily, on the other hand, falls in love with a son of local peasant, George. Old Aunt Agnes sends all the bunch off, first to Italy and then to India, so Emily would forget George, who is an undesirable partner for her because of class differences, and choose Cedric.","genres":["Comedy"],"stems":["Young","upper-class","fellow","Edward","arriv","with","his","friend","Cedric","at","the","famili","mans",",","Ivori","Hall",".","He","plan","to","pair","off","Cedric","with","his","sister","Emili",".","Emili",",","on","the","other","hand",",","fall","in","love","with","a","son","of","local","peasant",",","Georg",".","Old","Aunt","Agnes","send","all","the","bunch","off",",","first","to","Itali","and","then","to","India",",","so","Emili","would","forget","Georg",",","who","is","an","undesir","partner","for","her","becaus","of","class","differ",",","and","choos","Cedric","."],"lemmas":["young","upper-class","fellow","Edward","arrive","with","he","friend","Cedric","at","the","family","manse",",","Ivory","Hall",".","he","plan","to","pair","off","Cedric","with","he","sister","Emily",".","Emily",",","on","the","other","hand",",","fall","in","love","with","a","son","of","local","peasant",",","George",".","Old","Aunt","Agnes","send","all","the","bunch","off",",","first","to","Italy","and","then","to","India",",","so","Emily","would","forget","George",",","who","be","a","undesirable","partner","for","she","because","of","class","difference",",","and","choose","Cedric","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Young upper-class fellow","upper-class fellow Edward","fellow Edward arrives","Edward arrives with","arrives with his","with his friend","his friend Cedric","friend Cedric at","Cedric at the","at the family","the family manse","family manse ,","manse , Ivory",", Ivory Hall","He plans to","plans to pair","to pair off","pair off Cedric","off Cedric with","Cedric with his","with his sister","his sister Emily","Emily , on",", on the","on the other","the other hand","other hand ,","hand , falls",", falls in","falls in love","in love with","love with a","with a son","a son of","son of local","of local peasant","local peasant ,","peasant , George","Old Aunt Agnes","Aunt Agnes sends","Agnes sends all","sends all the","all the bunch","the bunch off","bunch off ,","off , first",", first to","first to Italy","to Italy and","Italy and then","and then to","then to India","to India ,","India , so",", so Emily","so Emily would","Emily would forget","would forget George","forget George ,","George , who",", who is","who is an","is an undesirable","an undesirable partner","undesirable partner for","partner for her","for her because","her because of","because of class","of class differences","class differences ,","differences , and",", and choose","and choose Cedric"],"2grams":["Young upper-class","upper-class fellow","fellow Edward","Edward arrives","arrives with","with his","his friend","friend Cedric","Cedric at","at the","the family","family manse","manse ,",", Ivory","Ivory Hall","He plans","plans to","to pair","pair off","off Cedric","Cedric with","with his","his sister","sister Emily","Emily ,",", on","on the","the other","other hand","hand ,",", falls","falls in","in love","love with","with a","a son","son of","of local","local peasant","peasant ,",", George","Old Aunt","Aunt Agnes","Agnes sends","sends all","all the","the bunch","bunch off","off ,",", first","first to","to Italy","Italy and","and then","then to","to India","India ,",", so","so Emily","Emily would","would forget","forget George","George ,",", who","who is","is an","an undesirable","undesirable partner","partner for","for her","her because","because of","of class","class differences","differences ,",", and","and choose","choose Cedric"]}