{"title":"Showdown","plot":"Ken has just moved from Kansas with his mother. He talks to a girl named Julie, not knowing that her boyfriend Tom is very possessive of her. Tom is learning karate from Lee, a sensei whose brother was killed by a rookie cop named Billy. Billy has since then become the janitor of the school that Ken, Julie and Tom go to. When Ken gets beaten up by Tom for talking to Julie again, Billy helps Ken by teaching him how to defend himself, which eventually leads to a battle between student vs. student, and sensei vs. sensei.","genres":["Action"],"stems":["Ken","has","just","move","from","Kansa","with","his","mother",".","He","talk","to","a","girl","name","Juli",",","not","know","that","her","boyfriend","Tom","is","veri","possess","of","her",".","Tom","is","learn","karat","from","Lee",",","a","sensei","whose","brother","was","kill","by","a","rooki","cop","name","Billi",".","Billi","has","sinc","then","becom","the","janitor","of","the","school","that","Ken",",","Juli","and","Tom","go","to",".","When","Ken","get","beaten","up","by","Tom","for","talk","to","Juli","again",",","Billi","help","Ken","by","teach","him","how","to","defend","himself",",","which","eventu","lead","to","a","battl","between","student","vs.","student",",","and","sensei","vs.","sensei","."],"lemmas":["Ken","have","just","move","from","Kansas","with","he","mother",".","he","talk","to","a","girl","name","Julie",",","not","know","that","she","boyfriend","Tom","be","very","possessive","of","she",".","Tom","be","learn","karate","from","Lee",",","a","sensei","whose","brother","be","kill","by","a","rookie","cop","name","Billy",".","Billy","have","since","then","become","the","janitor","of","the","school","that","Ken",",","Julie","and","Tom","go","to",".","when","Ken","get","beat","up","by","Tom","for","talk","to","Julie","again",",","Billy","help","Ken","by","teach","he","how","to","defend","himself",",","which","eventually","lead","to","a","battle","between","student","vs.","student",",","and","sensei","vs.","sensei","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Ken has just","has just moved","just moved from","moved from Kansas","from Kansas with","Kansas with his","with his mother","He talks to","talks to a","to a girl","a girl named","girl named Julie","named Julie ,","Julie , not",", not knowing","not knowing that","knowing that her","that her boyfriend","her boyfriend Tom","boyfriend Tom is","Tom is very","is very possessive","very possessive of","possessive of her","Tom is learning","is learning karate","learning karate from","karate from Lee","from Lee ,","Lee , a",", a sensei","a sensei whose","sensei whose brother","whose brother was","brother was killed","was killed by","killed by a","by a rookie","a rookie cop","rookie cop named","cop named Billy","Billy has since","has since then","since then become","then become the","become the janitor","the janitor of","janitor of the","of the school","the school that","school that Ken","that Ken ,","Ken , Julie",", Julie and","Julie and Tom","and Tom go","Tom go to","When Ken gets","Ken gets beaten","gets beaten up","beaten up by","up by Tom","by Tom for","Tom for talking","for talking to","talking to Julie","to Julie again","Julie again ,","again , Billy",", Billy helps","Billy helps Ken","helps Ken by","Ken by teaching","by teaching him","teaching him how","him how to","how to defend","to defend himself","defend himself ,","himself , which",", which eventually","which eventually leads","eventually leads to","leads to a","to a battle","a battle between","battle between student","between student vs.","student vs. student","vs. student ,","student , and",", and sensei","and sensei vs.","sensei vs. sensei"],"2grams":["Ken has","has just","just moved","moved from","from Kansas","Kansas with","with his","his mother","He talks","talks to","to a","a girl","girl named","named Julie","Julie ,",", not","not knowing","knowing that","that her","her boyfriend","boyfriend Tom","Tom is","is very","very possessive","possessive of","of her","Tom is","is learning","learning karate","karate from","from Lee","Lee ,",", a","a sensei","sensei whose","whose brother","brother was","was killed","killed by","by a","a rookie","rookie cop","cop named","named Billy","Billy has","has since","since then","then become","become the","the janitor","janitor of","of the","the school","school that","that Ken","Ken ,",", Julie","Julie and","and Tom","Tom go","go to","When Ken","Ken gets","gets beaten","beaten up","up by","by Tom","Tom for","for talking","talking to","to Julie","Julie again","again ,",", Billy","Billy helps","helps Ken","Ken by","by teaching","teaching him","him how","how to","to defend","defend himself","himself ,",", which","which eventually","eventually leads","leads to","to a","a battle","battle between","between student","student vs.","vs. student","student ,",", and","and sensei","sensei vs.","vs. sensei"]}