{"title":"Raja Kumarudu","plot":"After the passing away of his parents, Raja lives with his uncle, Dhanraj, in Khandala, Maharashtra, India, where Dhanraj manages a hotel, while Raja is a model. While in Khandala, he meets with Rani, a guest from Punjab, and both fall in love with each other. Raja informs Dhanraj, who does not approve of Rani, and asks Raja to forget about her and marry his daughter instead. Will Raja do his uncle's bidding?","genres":["Comedy"," Romance"," Drama"],"stems":["After","the","pass","away","of","his","parent",",","Raja","live","with","his","uncl",",","Dhanraj",",","in","Khandala",",","Maharashtra",",","India",",","where","Dhanraj","manag","a","hotel",",","while","Raja","is","a","model",".","While","in","Khandala",",","he","meet","with","Rani",",","a","guest","from","Punjab",",","and","both","fall","in","love","with","each","other",".","Raja","inform","Dhanraj",",","who","doe","not","approv","of","Rani",",","and","ask","Raja","to","forget","about","her","and","marri","his","daughter","instead",".","Will","Raja","do","his","uncl","'s","bid","?"],"lemmas":["after","the","passing","away","of","he","parent",",","Raja","live","with","he","uncle",",","Dhanraj",",","in","Khandala",",","Maharashtra",",","India",",","where","Dhanraj","manage","a","hotel",",","while","Raja","be","a","model",".","while","in","Khandala",",","he","meet","with","Rani",",","a","guest","from","Punjab",",","and","both","fall","in","love","with","each","other",".","Raja","inform","Dhanraj",",","who","do","not","approve","of","Rani",",","and","ask","Raja","to","forget","about","she","and","marry","he","daughter","instead",".","Will","Raja","do","he","uncle","'s","bidding","?"],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["After the passing","the passing away","passing away of","away of his","of his parents","his parents ,","parents , Raja",", Raja lives","Raja lives with","lives with his","with his uncle","his uncle ,","uncle , Dhanraj",", Dhanraj ,","Dhanraj , in",", in Khandala","in Khandala ,","Khandala , Maharashtra",", Maharashtra ,","Maharashtra , India",", India ,","India , where",", where Dhanraj","where Dhanraj manages","Dhanraj manages a","manages a hotel","a hotel ,","hotel , while",", while Raja","while Raja is","Raja is a","is a model","While in Khandala","in Khandala ,","Khandala , he",", he meets","he meets with","meets with Rani","with Rani ,","Rani , a",", a guest","a guest from","guest from Punjab","from Punjab ,","Punjab , and",", and both","and both fall","both fall in","fall in love","in love with","love with each","with each other","Raja informs Dhanraj","informs Dhanraj ,","Dhanraj , who",", who does","who does not","does not approve","not approve of","approve of Rani","of Rani ,","Rani , and",", and asks","and asks Raja","asks Raja to","Raja to forget","to forget about","forget about her","about her and","her and marry","and marry his","marry his daughter","his daughter instead","Will Raja do","Raja do his","do his uncle","his uncle 's","uncle 's bidding"],"2grams":["After the","the passing","passing away","away of","of his","his parents","parents ,",", Raja","Raja lives","lives with","with his","his uncle","uncle ,",", Dhanraj","Dhanraj ,",", in","in Khandala","Khandala ,",", Maharashtra","Maharashtra ,",", India","India ,",", where","where Dhanraj","Dhanraj manages","manages a","a hotel","hotel ,",", while","while Raja","Raja is","is a","a model","While in","in Khandala","Khandala ,",", he","he meets","meets with","with Rani","Rani ,",", a","a guest","guest from","from Punjab","Punjab ,",", and","and both","both fall","fall in","in love","love with","with each","each other","Raja informs","informs Dhanraj","Dhanraj ,",", who","who does","does not","not approve","approve of","of Rani","Rani ,",", and","and asks","asks Raja","Raja to","to forget","forget about","about her","her and","and marry","marry his","his daughter","daughter instead","Will Raja","Raja do","do his","his uncle","uncle 's","'s bidding"]}