{"title":"Gypsy Boys","plot":"A look at the intertwined lives of a group of young gay men in San Francisco and their search for love. It focuses on two couples: Steven and Blair, and Manny and Aaron. Steven and Blair are a couple, but can't agree on how much of a relationship they want. Manny and Aaron are just good friends. Manny wants more, but Aaron is staying true to a long-distance relationship.","genres":["Comedy"," Drama"],"stems":["A","look","at","the","intertwin","live","of","a","group","of","young","gay","men","in","San","Francisco","and","their","search","for","love",".","It","focus","on","two","coupl",":","Steven","and","Blair",",","and","Manni","and","Aaron",".","Steven","and","Blair","are","a","coupl",",","but","ca","n't","agre","on","how","much","of","a","relationship","they","want",".","Manni","and","Aaron","are","just","good","friend",".","Manni","want","more",",","but","Aaron","is","stay","true","to","a","long-dist","relationship","."],"lemmas":["a","look","at","the","intertwine","life","of","a","group","of","young","gay","man","in","San","Francisco","and","they","search","for","love",".","it","focus","on","two","couple",":","Steven","and","Blair",",","and","Manny","and","Aaron",".","Steven","and","Blair","be","a","couple",",","but","can","not","agree","on","how","much","of","a","relationship","they","want",".","Manny","and","Aaron","be","just","good","friend",".","Manny","want","more",",","but","Aaron","be","stay","true","to","a","long-distance","relationship","."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["A look at","look at the","at the intertwined","the intertwined lives","intertwined lives of","lives of a","of a group","a group of","group of young","of young gay","young gay men","gay men in","men in San","in San Francisco","San Francisco and","Francisco and their","and their search","their search for","search for love","It focuses on","focuses on two","on two couples","two couples :","couples : Steven",": Steven and","Steven and Blair","and Blair ,","Blair , and",", and Manny","and Manny and","Manny and Aaron","Steven and Blair","and Blair are","Blair are a","are a couple","a couple ,","couple , but",", but ca","but ca n't","ca n't agree","n't agree on","agree on how","on how much","how much of","much of a","of a relationship","a relationship they","relationship they want","Manny and Aaron","and Aaron are","Aaron are just","are just good","just good friends","Manny wants more","wants more ,","more , but",", but Aaron","but Aaron is","Aaron is staying","is staying true","staying true to","true to a","to a long-distance","a long-distance relationship"],"2grams":["A look","look at","at the","the intertwined","intertwined lives","lives of","of a","a group","group of","of young","young gay","gay men","men in","in San","San Francisco","Francisco and","and their","their search","search for","for love","It focuses","focuses on","on two","two couples","couples :",": Steven","Steven and","and Blair","Blair ,",", and","and Manny","Manny and","and Aaron","Steven and","and Blair","Blair are","are a","a couple","couple ,",", but","but ca","ca n't","n't agree","agree on","on how","how much","much of","of a","a relationship","relationship they","they want","Manny and","and Aaron","Aaron are","are just","just good","good friends","Manny wants","wants more","more ,",", but","but Aaron","Aaron is","is staying","staying true","true to","to a","a long-distance","long-distance relationship"]}