{"title":"Quo Vadis","plot":"Marcus Vinicius meets Lygia in Rome and falls in love. But she is Christian and doesn't want anything to do with him. Marcus decides to kidnap her but Ursus, her bodyguard, catches Marcus. After that, Lygia falls in love, but Marcus must go to meet Nero. After the meeting somebody told Marcus that Nero burnt Rome. Marcus decides to go back to Rome and find Lygia.","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["Marcus","Vinicius","meet","Lygia","in","Rome","and","fall","in","love",".","But","she","is","Christian","and","doe","n't","want","anyth","to","do","with","him",".","Marcus","decid","to","kidnap","her","but","Ursus",",","her","bodyguard",",","catch","Marcus",".","After","that",",","Lygia","fall","in","love",",","but","Marcus","must","go","to","meet","Nero",".","After","the","meet","somebodi","told","Marcus","that","Nero","burnt","Rome",".","Marcus","decid","to","go","back","to","Rome","and","find","Lygia","."],"lemmas":["Marcus","Vinicius","meet","Lygia","in","Rome","and","fall","in","love",".","but","she","be","christian","and","do","not","want","anything","to","do","with","he",".","Marcus","decide","to","kidnap","she","but","Ursus",",","she","bodyguard",",","catch","Marcus",".","after","that",",","Lygia","fall","in","love",",","but","Marcus","must","go","to","meet","Nero",".","after","the","meeting","somebody","tell","Marcus","that","Nero","burn","Rome",".","Marcus","decide","to","go","back","to","Rome","and","find","Lygia","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","ORGANIZATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["Marcus Vinicius meets","Vinicius meets Lygia","meets Lygia in","Lygia in Rome","in Rome and","Rome and falls","and falls in","falls in love","But she is","she is Christian","is Christian and","Christian and does","and does n't","does n't want","n't want anything","want anything to","anything to do","to do with","do with him","Marcus decides to","decides to kidnap","to kidnap her","kidnap her but","her but Ursus","but Ursus ,","Ursus , her",", her bodyguard","her bodyguard ,","bodyguard , catches",", catches Marcus","After that ,","that , Lygia",", Lygia falls","Lygia falls in","falls in love","in love ,","love , but",", but Marcus","but Marcus must","Marcus must go","must go to","go to meet","to meet Nero","After the meeting","the meeting somebody","meeting somebody told","somebody told Marcus","told Marcus that","Marcus that Nero","that Nero burnt","Nero burnt Rome","Marcus decides to","decides to go","to go back","go back to","back to Rome","to Rome and","Rome and find","and find Lygia"],"2grams":["Marcus Vinicius","Vinicius meets","meets Lygia","Lygia in","in Rome","Rome and","and falls","falls in","in love","But she","she is","is Christian","Christian and","and does","does n't","n't want","want anything","anything to","to do","do with","with him","Marcus decides","decides to","to kidnap","kidnap her","her but","but Ursus","Ursus ,",", her","her bodyguard","bodyguard ,",", catches","catches Marcus","After that","that ,",", Lygia","Lygia falls","falls in","in love","love ,",", but","but Marcus","Marcus must","must go","go to","to meet","meet Nero","After the","the meeting","meeting somebody","somebody told","told Marcus","Marcus that","that Nero","Nero burnt","burnt Rome","Marcus decides","decides to","to go","go back","back to","to Rome","Rome and","and find","find Lygia"]}