{"title":"4 Young Barents Dox","plot":"A four-documentary mini series produced by Filmpool Nord in the Barents region with four young directors from Norway, Sweden, Finland, and Russia each directing a 28-minute documentary of their choice. Includes Anton by Reuben Sletten, Trackback by Anette Niia, Before the Flood by Mika Ronkainen, and Jazz de Gas by Sergej Jigaltsov.","genres":["Documentary"],"stems":["A","four-documentari","mini","seri","produc","by","Filmpool","Nord","in","the","Barent","region","with","four","young","director","from","Norway",",","Sweden",",","Finland",",","and","Russia","each","direct","a","28-minut","documentari","of","their","choic",".","Include","Anton","by","Reuben","Sletten",",","Trackback","by","Anett","Niia",",","Befor","the","Flood","by","Mika","Ronkainen",",","and","Jazz","de","Gas","by","Sergej","Jigaltsov","."],"lemmas":["a","four-documentary","mini","series","produce","by","Filmpool","Nord","in","the","Barents","region","with","four","young","director","from","Norway",",","Sweden",",","Finland",",","and","Russia","each","direct","a","28-minute","documentary","of","they","choice",".","include","Anton","by","Reuben","Sletten",",","Trackback","by","Anette","Niia",",","before","the","Flood","by","Mika","Ronkainen",",","and","jazz","de","Gas","by","Sergej","Jigaltsov","."],"named_entities":["ORGANIZATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","ORGANIZATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["A four-documentary mini","four-documentary mini series","mini series produced","series produced by","produced by Filmpool","by Filmpool Nord","Filmpool Nord in","Nord in the","in the Barents","the Barents region","Barents region with","region with four","with four young","four young directors","young directors from","directors from Norway","from Norway ,","Norway , Sweden",", Sweden ,","Sweden , Finland",", Finland ,","Finland , and",", and Russia","and Russia each","Russia each directing","each directing a","directing a 28-minute","a 28-minute documentary","28-minute documentary of","documentary of their","of their choice","Includes Anton by","Anton by Reuben","by Reuben Sletten","Reuben Sletten ,","Sletten , Trackback",", Trackback by","Trackback by Anette","by Anette Niia","Anette Niia ,","Niia , Before",", Before the","Before the Flood","the Flood by","Flood by Mika","by Mika Ronkainen","Mika Ronkainen ,","Ronkainen , and",", and Jazz","and Jazz de","Jazz de Gas","de Gas by","Gas by Sergej","by Sergej Jigaltsov"],"2grams":["A four-documentary","four-documentary mini","mini series","series produced","produced by","by Filmpool","Filmpool Nord","Nord in","in the","the Barents","Barents region","region with","with four","four young","young directors","directors from","from Norway","Norway ,",", Sweden","Sweden ,",", Finland","Finland ,",", and","and Russia","Russia each","each directing","directing a","a 28-minute","28-minute documentary","documentary of","of their","their choice","Includes Anton","Anton by","by Reuben","Reuben Sletten","Sletten ,",", Trackback","Trackback by","by Anette","Anette Niia","Niia ,",", Before","Before the","the Flood","Flood by","by Mika","Mika Ronkainen","Ronkainen ,",", and","and Jazz","Jazz de","de Gas","Gas by","by Sergej","Sergej Jigaltsov"]}