{"title":"Nuvvu Naaku Nachchav","plot":"Venakteswarlu alias Venky (Venkatesh) comes to the house of Murthy (Prakash Raj) on recommendation of his father Sekhar (Chandra Mohan) who is a childhood friend of Murthy. Nandini alias Nandu (Arti Agarwal) is the daughter of Murthy. Venky enters that place when Nandu is about to get engaged to a software professional from the USA. Soon, Venky bonds with everyone from Murthy's family. Murthy helps Venky secure a job. The relationship between Venky and Nandu starts with hatred and turns into friendship. Nandu confesses her love for Venky to him. Venky, who does not want to spoil the relationship between their parents, decides to leave the house. But Murthy goes to the railway station and talks to Venky, which causes Venky to return. On his return, Nandu stops speaking to him. When Venky accompanies Nandu and Pinky (Nandu's cousin) to Nandu's friend Asha's wedding, sparks fly between them.Even though Venky also is in love with Nandu, he does not express it and pretends to not have feelings for Nandu. When they get back, its time for Nandu's wedding! Venky takes the onus of running the show of marriage. The demure Nandu is shattered.Circumstances lead to everyone finding out about Venky and Nandu. What follows, and how Nandu and Venky end up together forms the climax of the story.","genres":["Comedy"," Musical"," Family"],"stems":["Venakteswarlu","alia","Venki","(","Venkatesh",")","come","to","the","hous","of","Murthi","(","Prakash","Raj",")","on","recommend","of","his","father","Sekhar","(","Chandra","Mohan",")","who","is","a","childhood","friend","of","Murthi",".","Nandini","alia","Nandu","(","Arti","Agarwal",")","is","the","daughter","of","Murthi",".","Venki","enter","that","place","when","Nandu","is","about","to","get","engag","to","a","softwar","profession","from","the","USA",".","Soon",",","Venki","bond","with","everyon","from","Murthi","'s","famili",".","Murthi","help","Venki","secur","a","job",".","The","relationship","between","Venki","and","Nandu","start","with","hatr","and","turn","into","friendship",".","Nandu","confess","her","love","for","Venki","to","him",".","Venki",",","who","doe","not","want","to","spoil","the","relationship","between","their","parent",",","decid","to","leav","the","hous",".","But","Murthi","goe","to","the","railway","station","and","talk","to","Venki",",","which","caus","Venki","to","return",".","On","his","return",",","Nandu","stop","speak","to","him",".","When","Venki","accompani","Nandu","and","Pinki","(","Nandu","'s","cousin",")","to","Nandu","'s","friend","Asha","'s","wed",",","spark","fli","between","them.Even","though","Venki","also","is","in","love","with","Nandu",",","he","doe","not","express","it","and","pretend","to","not","have","feel","for","Nandu",".","When","they","get","back",",","it","time","for","Nandu","'s","wed","!","Venki","take","the","onus","of","run","the","show","of","marriag",".","The","demur","Nandu","is","shattered.Circumst","lead","to","everyon","find","out","about","Venki","and","Nandu",".","What","follow",",","and","how","Nandu","and","Venki","end","up","togeth","form","the","climax","of","the","stori","."],"lemmas":["Venakteswarlu","alia","Venky","-lrb-","Venkatesh","-rrb-","come","to","the","house","of","Murthy","-lrb-","Prakash","Raj","-rrb-","on","recommendation","of","he","father","Sekhar","-lrb-","Chandra","Mohan","-rrb-","who","be","a","childhood","friend","of","Murthy",".","Nandini","alia","Nandu","-lrb-","Arti","Agarwal","-rrb-","be","the","daughter","of","Murthy",".","Venky","enter","that","place","when","Nandu","be","about","to","get","engage","to","a","software","professional","from","the","USA",".","soon",",","Venky","bond","with","everyone","from","Murthy","'s","family",".","Murthy","help","Venky","secure","a","job",".","the","relationship","between","Venky","and","Nandu","start","with","hatred","and","turn","into","friendship",".","Nandu","confess","she","love","for","Venky","to","he",".","Venky",",","who","do","not","want","to","spoil","the","relationship","between","they","parent",",","decide","to","leave","the","house",".","but","Murthy","go","to","the","railway","station","and","talk","to","Venky",",","which","cause","Venky","to","return",".","on","he","return",",","Nandu","stop","speak","to","he",".","when","Venky","accompany","Nandu","and","Pinky","-lrb-","Nandu","'s","cousin","-rrb-","to","Nandu","'s","friend","Asha","'s","wedding",",","spark","fly","between","them.Even","though","Venky","also","be","in","love","with","Nandu",",","he","do","not","express","it","and","pretend","to","not","have","feeling","for","Nandu",".","when","they","get","back",",","its","time","for","Nandu","'s","wedding","!","Venky","take","the","onus","of","run","the","show","of","marriage",".","the","demure","Nandu","be","shattered.circumstances","lead","to","everyone","find","out","about","Venky","and","Nandu",".","what","follow",",","and","how","Nandu","and","Venky","end","up","together","form","the","climax","of","the","story","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["Venakteswarlu alias Venky","alias Venky (","Venky ( Venkatesh","( Venkatesh )","Venkatesh ) comes",") comes to","comes to the","to the house","the house of","house of Murthy","of Murthy (","Murthy ( Prakash","( Prakash Raj","Prakash Raj )","Raj ) on",") on recommendation","on recommendation of","recommendation of his","of his father","his father Sekhar","father Sekhar (","Sekhar ( Chandra","( Chandra Mohan","Chandra Mohan )","Mohan ) who",") who is","who is a","is a childhood","a childhood friend","childhood friend of","friend of Murthy","Nandini alias Nandu","alias Nandu (","Nandu ( Arti","( Arti Agarwal","Arti Agarwal )","Agarwal ) is",") is the","is the daughter","the daughter of","daughter of Murthy","Venky enters that","enters that place","that place when","place when Nandu","when Nandu is","Nandu is about","is about to","about to get","to get engaged","get engaged to","engaged to a","to a software","a software professional","software professional from","professional from the","from the USA","Soon , Venky",", Venky bonds","Venky bonds with","bonds with everyone","with everyone from","everyone from Murthy","from Murthy 's","Murthy 's family","Murthy helps Venky","helps Venky secure","Venky secure a","secure a job","The relationship between","relationship between Venky","between Venky and","Venky and Nandu","and Nandu starts","Nandu starts with","starts with hatred","with hatred and","hatred and turns","and turns into","turns into friendship","Nandu confesses her","confesses her love","her love for","love for Venky","for Venky to","Venky to him","Venky , who",", who does","who does not","does not want","not want to","want to spoil","to spoil the","spoil the relationship","the relationship between","relationship between their","between their parents","their parents ,","parents , decides",", decides to","decides to leave","to leave the","leave the house","But Murthy goes","Murthy goes to","goes to the","to the railway","the railway station","railway station and","station and talks","and talks to","talks to Venky","to Venky ,","Venky , which",", which causes","which causes Venky","causes Venky to","Venky to return","On his return","his return ,","return , Nandu",", Nandu stops","Nandu stops speaking","stops speaking to","speaking to him","When Venky accompanies","Venky accompanies Nandu","accompanies Nandu and","Nandu and Pinky","and Pinky (","Pinky ( Nandu","( Nandu 's","Nandu 's cousin","'s cousin )","cousin ) to",") to Nandu","to Nandu 's","Nandu 's friend","'s friend Asha","friend Asha 's","Asha 's wedding","'s wedding ,","wedding , sparks",", sparks fly","sparks fly between","fly between them.Even","between them.Even though","them.Even though Venky","though Venky also","Venky also is","also is in","is in love","in love with","love with Nandu","with Nandu ,","Nandu , he",", he does","he does not","does not express","not express it","express it and","it and pretends","and pretends to","pretends to not","to not have","not have feelings","have feelings for","feelings for Nandu","When they get","they get back","get back ,","back , its",", its time","its time for","time for Nandu","for Nandu 's","Nandu 's wedding","Venky takes the","takes the onus","the onus of","onus of running","of running the","running the show","the show of","show of marriage","The demure Nandu","demure Nandu is","Nandu is shattered.Circumstances","is shattered.Circumstances lead","shattered.Circumstances lead to","lead to everyone","to everyone finding","everyone finding out","finding out about","out about Venky","about Venky and","Venky and Nandu","What follows ,","follows , and",", and how","and how Nandu","how Nandu and","Nandu and Venky","and Venky end","Venky end up","end up together","up together forms","together forms the","forms the climax","the climax of","climax of the","of the story"],"2grams":["Venakteswarlu alias","alias Venky","Venky (","( Venkatesh","Venkatesh )",") comes","comes to","to the","the house","house of","of Murthy","Murthy (","( Prakash","Prakash Raj","Raj )",") on","on recommendation","recommendation of","of his","his father","father Sekhar","Sekhar (","( Chandra","Chandra Mohan","Mohan )",") who","who is","is a","a childhood","childhood friend","friend of","of Murthy","Nandini alias","alias Nandu","Nandu (","( Arti","Arti Agarwal","Agarwal )",") is","is the","the daughter","daughter of","of Murthy","Venky enters","enters that","that place","place when","when Nandu","Nandu is","is about","about to","to get","get engaged","engaged to","to a","a software","software professional","professional from","from the","the USA","Soon ,",", Venky","Venky bonds","bonds with","with everyone","everyone from","from Murthy","Murthy 's","'s family","Murthy helps","helps Venky","Venky secure","secure a","a job","The relationship","relationship between","between Venky","Venky and","and Nandu","Nandu starts","starts with","with hatred","hatred and","and turns","turns into","into friendship","Nandu confesses","confesses her","her love","love for","for Venky","Venky to","to him","Venky ,",", who","who does","does not","not want","want to","to spoil","spoil the","the relationship","relationship between","between their","their parents","parents ,",", decides","decides to","to leave","leave the","the house","But Murthy","Murthy goes","goes to","to the","the railway","railway station","station and","and talks","talks to","to Venky","Venky ,",", which","which causes","causes Venky","Venky to","to return","On his","his return","return ,",", Nandu","Nandu stops","stops speaking","speaking to","to him","When Venky","Venky accompanies","accompanies Nandu","Nandu and","and Pinky","Pinky (","( Nandu","Nandu 's","'s cousin","cousin )",") to","to Nandu","Nandu 's","'s friend","friend Asha","Asha 's","'s wedding","wedding ,",", sparks","sparks fly","fly between","between them.Even","them.Even though","though Venky","Venky also","also is","is in","in love","love with","with Nandu","Nandu ,",", he","he does","does not","not express","express it","it and","and pretends","pretends to","to not","not have","have feelings","feelings for","for Nandu","When they","they get","get back","back ,",", its","its time","time for","for Nandu","Nandu 's","'s wedding","Venky takes","takes the","the onus","onus of","of running","running the","the show","show of","of marriage","The demure","demure Nandu","Nandu is","is shattered.Circumstances","shattered.Circumstances lead","lead to","to everyone","everyone finding","finding out","out about","about Venky","Venky and","and Nandu","What follows","follows ,",", and","and how","how Nandu","Nandu and","and Venky","Venky end","end up","up together","together forms","forms the","the climax","climax of","of the","the story"]}