{"title":"Eager Bodies","plot":"Paul and Charlotte are in love. Charlotte discovers she has a grave malady and Paul supports her. But Paul is also attracted to Ninon, another girl. Charlotte accepts Paul to have an affair with her, and the three start a difficult and ambiguous relationship.","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["Paul","and","Charlott","are","in","love",".","Charlott","discov","she","has","a","grave","maladi","and","Paul","support","her",".","But","Paul","is","also","attract","to","Ninon",",","anoth","girl",".","Charlott","accept","Paul","to","have","an","affair","with","her",",","and","the","three","start","a","difficult","and","ambigu","relationship","."],"lemmas":["Paul","and","Charlotte","be","in","love",".","Charlotte","discover","she","have","a","grave","malady","and","Paul","support","she",".","but","Paul","be","also","attract","to","Ninon",",","another","girl",".","Charlotte","accept","Paul","to","have","a","affair","with","she",",","and","the","three","start","a","difficult","and","ambiguous","relationship","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["Paul and Charlotte","and Charlotte are","Charlotte are in","are in love","Charlotte discovers she","discovers she has","she has a","has a grave","a grave malady","grave malady and","malady and Paul","and Paul supports","Paul supports her","But Paul is","Paul is also","is also attracted","also attracted to","attracted to Ninon","to Ninon ,","Ninon , another",", another girl","Charlotte accepts Paul","accepts Paul to","Paul to have","to have an","have an affair","an affair with","affair with her","with her ,","her , and",", and the","and the three","the three start","three start a","start a difficult","a difficult and","difficult and ambiguous","and ambiguous relationship"],"2grams":["Paul and","and Charlotte","Charlotte are","are in","in love","Charlotte discovers","discovers she","she has","has a","a grave","grave malady","malady and","and Paul","Paul supports","supports her","But Paul","Paul is","is also","also attracted","attracted to","to Ninon","Ninon ,",", another","another girl","Charlotte accepts","accepts Paul","Paul to","to have","have an","an affair","affair with","with her","her ,",", and","and the","the three","three start","start a","a difficult","difficult and","and ambiguous","ambiguous relationship"]}