{"title":"The Room","plot":"In San Francisco, we follow Johnny, a man who has a girlfriend, Lisa, and also his best friend, Mark. Lisa has been cheating on Johnny with Mark and Johnny doesn't know! Will Johnny ever find out? Will Mark still be Johnny's best friend?","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["In","San","Francisco",",","we","follow","Johnni",",","a","man","who","has","a","girlfriend",",","Lisa",",","and","also","his","best","friend",",","Mark",".","Lisa","has","been","cheat","on","Johnni","with","Mark","and","Johnni","doe","n't","know","!","Will","Johnni","ever","find","out","?","Will","Mark","still","be","Johnni","'s","best","friend","?"],"lemmas":["in","San","Francisco",",","we","follow","Johnny",",","a","man","who","have","a","girlfriend",",","Lisa",",","and","also","he","best","friend",",","Mark",".","Lisa","have","be","cheat","on","Johnny","with","Mark","and","Johnny","do","not","know","!","Will","Johnny","ever","find","out","?","Will","Mark","still","be","Johnny","'s","best","friend","?"],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["In San Francisco","San Francisco ,","Francisco , we",", we follow","we follow Johnny","follow Johnny ,","Johnny , a",", a man","a man who","man who has","who has a","has a girlfriend","a girlfriend ,","girlfriend , Lisa",", Lisa ,","Lisa , and",", and also","and also his","also his best","his best friend","best friend ,","friend , Mark","Lisa has been","has been cheating","been cheating on","cheating on Johnny","on Johnny with","Johnny with Mark","with Mark and","Mark and Johnny","and Johnny does","Johnny does n't","does n't know","Will Johnny ever","Johnny ever find","ever find out","Will Mark still","Mark still be","still be Johnny","be Johnny 's","Johnny 's best","'s best friend"],"2grams":["In San","San Francisco","Francisco ,",", we","we follow","follow Johnny","Johnny ,",", a","a man","man who","who has","has a","a girlfriend","girlfriend ,",", Lisa","Lisa ,",", and","and also","also his","his best","best friend","friend ,",", Mark","Lisa has","has been","been cheating","cheating on","on Johnny","Johnny with","with Mark","Mark and","and Johnny","Johnny does","does n't","n't know","Will Johnny","Johnny ever","ever find","find out","Will Mark","Mark still","still be","be Johnny","Johnny 's","'s best","best friend"]}