{"title":"Missing Brendan","plot":"George takes a trip to Vietnam to find his missing son. George's son Bob and Bob's son Patrick accompany George on the trip. George's son, Brendan, has been Missing in Action since the ...","genres":["Drama"," War"," Romance"],"stems":["Georg","take","a","trip","to","Vietnam","to","find","his","miss","son",".","Georg","'s","son","Bob","and","Bob","'s","son","Patrick","accompani","Georg","on","the","trip",".","Georg","'s","son",",","Brendan",",","has","been","Miss","in","Action","sinc","the","..."],"lemmas":["George","take","a","trip","to","Vietnam","to","find","he","miss","son",".","George","'s","son","Bob","and","Bob","'s","son","Patrick","accompany","George","on","the","trip",".","George","'s","son",",","Brendan",",","have","be","miss","in","Action","since","the","..."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["George takes a","takes a trip","a trip to","trip to Vietnam","to Vietnam to","Vietnam to find","to find his","find his missing","his missing son","George 's son","'s son Bob","son Bob and","Bob and Bob","and Bob 's","Bob 's son","'s son Patrick","son Patrick accompany","Patrick accompany George","accompany George on","George on the","on the trip","George 's son","'s son ,","son , Brendan",", Brendan ,","Brendan , has",", has been","has been Missing","been Missing in","Missing in Action","in Action since","Action since the","since the ..."],"2grams":["George takes","takes a","a trip","trip to","to Vietnam","Vietnam to","to find","find his","his missing","missing son","George 's","'s son","son Bob","Bob and","and Bob","Bob 's","'s son","son Patrick","Patrick accompany","accompany George","George on","on the","the trip","George 's","'s son","son ,",", Brendan","Brendan ,",", has","has been","been Missing","Missing in","in Action","Action since","since the","the ..."]}