{"title":"Bunny","plot":"Somaraju (Prakash Raj ) is a leading business man in Visakhapatnam . Mysamma (Mukesh Rishi ) is a close member of Somaraju, who handles the deals of Somaraju in Hyderabad . Mahalaxmi (Gowri...","genres":["Action"," Drama"],"stems":["Somaraju","(","Prakash","Raj",")","is","a","lead","busi","man","in","Visakhapatnam",".","Mysamma","(","Mukesh","Rishi",")","is","a","close","member","of","Somaraju",",","who","handl","the","deal","of","Somaraju","in","Hyderabad",".","Mahalaxmi","(","Gowri","..."],"lemmas":["Somaraju","-lrb-","Prakash","Raj","-rrb-","be","a","lead","business","man","in","Visakhapatnam",".","Mysamma","-lrb-","Mukesh","Rishi","-rrb-","be","a","close","member","of","Somaraju",",","who","handle","the","deal","of","Somaraju","in","Hyderabad",".","Mahalaxmi","-lrb-","Gowri","..."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["Somaraju ( Prakash","( Prakash Raj","Prakash Raj )","Raj ) is",") is a","is a leading","a leading business","leading business man","business man in","man in Visakhapatnam","Mysamma ( Mukesh","( Mukesh Rishi","Mukesh Rishi )","Rishi ) is",") is a","is a close","a close member","close member of","member of Somaraju","of Somaraju ,","Somaraju , who",", who handles","who handles the","handles the deals","the deals of","deals of Somaraju","of Somaraju in","Somaraju in Hyderabad","Mahalaxmi ( Gowri","( Gowri ..."],"2grams":["Somaraju (","( Prakash","Prakash Raj","Raj )",") is","is a","a leading","leading business","business man","man in","in Visakhapatnam","Mysamma (","( Mukesh","Mukesh Rishi","Rishi )",") is","is a","a close","close member","member of","of Somaraju","Somaraju ,",", who","who handles","handles the","the deals","deals of","of Somaraju","Somaraju in","in Hyderabad","Mahalaxmi (","( Gowri","Gowri ..."]}