{"title":"Texxas Jam '78","plot":"The first real look at an event that crammed 100,000 people into the Cotton Bowl in Dallas, Texas to celebrate Rock n' Roll in 1978. The all day concert featured Aerosmith, Heart, Journey, Eddie Money, Head East, Frank Marino and the Mahagony Rush, Tedd Nugent, and others!!!","genres":["Documentary"],"stems":["The","first","real","look","at","an","event","that","cram","100,000","peopl","into","the","Cotton","Bowl","in","Dalla",",","Texa","to","celebr","Rock","n","'","Roll","in","1978",".","The","all","day","concert","featur","Aerosmith",",","Heart",",","Journey",",","Eddie","Money",",","Head","East",",","Frank","Marino","and","the","Mahagoni","Rush",",","Tedd","Nugent",",","and","other","!!!"],"lemmas":["the","first","real","look","at","a","event","that","cram","100,000","people","into","the","Cotton","Bowl","in","Dallas",",","Texas","to","celebrate","Rock","n","'","Roll","in","1978",".","the","all","day","concert","feature","Aerosmith",",","Heart",",","Journey",",","Eddie","Money",",","Head","East",",","Frank","Marino","and","the","Mahagony","Rush",",","Tedd","Nugent",",","and","other","!!!"],"named_entities":["LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","ORGANIZATION","ORGANIZATION","ORGANIZATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["The first real","first real look","real look at","look at an","at an event","an event that","event that crammed","that crammed 100,000","crammed 100,000 people","100,000 people into","people into the","into the Cotton","the Cotton Bowl","Cotton Bowl in","Bowl in Dallas","in Dallas ,","Dallas , Texas",", Texas to","Texas to celebrate","to celebrate Rock","celebrate Rock n","Rock n '","n ' Roll","' Roll in","Roll in 1978","The all day","all day concert","day concert featured","concert featured Aerosmith","featured Aerosmith ,","Aerosmith , Heart",", Heart ,","Heart , Journey",", Journey ,","Journey , Eddie",", Eddie Money","Eddie Money ,","Money , Head",", Head East","Head East ,","East , Frank",", Frank Marino","Frank Marino and","Marino and the","and the Mahagony","the Mahagony Rush","Mahagony Rush ,","Rush , Tedd",", Tedd Nugent","Tedd Nugent ,","Nugent , and",", and others","and others !!!"],"2grams":["The first","first real","real look","look at","at an","an event","event that","that crammed","crammed 100,000","100,000 people","people into","into the","the Cotton","Cotton Bowl","Bowl in","in Dallas","Dallas ,",", Texas","Texas to","to celebrate","celebrate Rock","Rock n","n '","' Roll","Roll in","in 1978","The all","all day","day concert","concert featured","featured Aerosmith","Aerosmith ,",", Heart","Heart ,",", Journey","Journey ,",", Eddie","Eddie Money","Money ,",", Head","Head East","East ,",", Frank","Frank Marino","Marino and","and the","the Mahagony","Mahagony Rush","Rush ,",", Tedd","Tedd Nugent","Nugent ,",", and","and others","others !!!"]}