{"title":"Overhearing Ron","plot":"Overhearing Ron is the story of Liza Henry. Liza is looking for the mythic icon, Ron Shapiro, in small town Oxford, Mississippi. Accompanied by her fiancée, Ian, she interviews the town's residents. As they go, Liza and Ian realize that they need Ron to save their relationship and maybe the rest of their lives.","genres":["Drama"," Romance"],"stems":["Overhear","Ron","is","the","stori","of","Liza","Henri",".","Liza","is","look","for","the","mythic","icon",",","Ron","Shapiro",",","in","small","town","Oxford",",","Mississippi",".","Accompani","by","her","fiancé",",","Ian",",","she","interview","the","town","'s","resid",".","As","they","go",",","Liza","and","Ian","realiz","that","they","need","Ron","to","save","their","relationship","and","mayb","the","rest","of","their","live","."],"lemmas":["Overhearing","Ron","be","the","story","of","Liza","Henry",".","Liza","be","look","for","the","mythic","icon",",","Ron","Shapiro",",","in","small","town","Oxford",",","Mississippi",".","accompany","by","she","fiancée",",","Ian",",","she","interview","the","town","'s","resident",".","as","they","go",",","Liza","and","Ian","realize","that","they","need","Ron","to","save","they","relationship","and","maybe","the","rest","of","they","life","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Overhearing Ron is","Ron is the","is the story","the story of","story of Liza","of Liza Henry","Liza is looking","is looking for","looking for the","for the mythic","the mythic icon","mythic icon ,","icon , Ron",", Ron Shapiro","Ron Shapiro ,","Shapiro , in",", in small","in small town","small town Oxford","town Oxford ,","Oxford , Mississippi","Accompanied by her","by her fiancée","her fiancée ,","fiancée , Ian",", Ian ,","Ian , she",", she interviews","she interviews the","interviews the town","the town 's","town 's residents","As they go","they go ,","go , Liza",", Liza and","Liza and Ian","and Ian realize","Ian realize that","realize that they","that they need","they need Ron","need Ron to","Ron to save","to save their","save their relationship","their relationship and","relationship and maybe","and maybe the","maybe the rest","the rest of","rest of their","of their lives"],"2grams":["Overhearing Ron","Ron is","is the","the story","story of","of Liza","Liza Henry","Liza is","is looking","looking for","for the","the mythic","mythic icon","icon ,",", Ron","Ron Shapiro","Shapiro ,",", in","in small","small town","town Oxford","Oxford ,",", Mississippi","Accompanied by","by her","her fiancée","fiancée ,",", Ian","Ian ,",", she","she interviews","interviews the","the town","town 's","'s residents","As they","they go","go ,",", Liza","Liza and","and Ian","Ian realize","realize that","that they","they need","need Ron","Ron to","to save","save their","their relationship","relationship and","and maybe","maybe the","the rest","rest of","of their","their lives"]}