{"title":"Digimon: Island of the Lost Digimon","plot":"While traveling on Ball the Trailmon, Takuya, Koji, JP, Tommy, Zoe, Neemon, and Bokomon end up on the Wandering Island where the Human-type Digimon (led by D'Arcmon) and the Beast-type Digimon (led by HippoGryphomon) are at war with each other. Takuya and Co. befriend Bearmon (younger brother of Grizzlymon) and Kotemon (younger brother of Dinohyumon) who are friends. Takuya sides with Dinohyumon and the Human-type Digimon and Koji sides with Grizzlymon and the Beast-type Digimon. When they hear the legend that the bird Ornismon can end the war, Zoe, JP, and Tommy help Bearmon, Kotemon, and the Baby and In-Training Digimon into reassembling Ornismon's picture. Is the legend true? And what are the connections between D'Arcmon, HippoGryphomon, and the evil Murmuxmon?","genres":["Action"," Adventure"],"stems":["While","travel","on","Ball","the","Trailmon",",","Takuya",",","Koji",",","JP",",","Tommi",",","Zoe",",","Neemon",",","and","Bokomon","end","up","on","the","Wander","Island","where","the","Human-typ","Digimon","(","led","by","D'Arcmon",")","and","the","Beast-typ","Digimon","(","led","by","HippoGryphomon",")","are","at","war","with","each","other",".","Takuya","and","Co.","befriend","Bearmon","(","younger","brother","of","Grizzlymon",")","and","Kotemon","(","younger","brother","of","Dinohyumon",")","who","are","friend",".","Takuya","side","with","Dinohyumon","and","the","Human-typ","Digimon","and","Koji","side","with","Grizzlymon","and","the","Beast-typ","Digimon",".","When","they","hear","the","legend","that","the","bird","Ornismon","can","end","the","war",",","Zoe",",","JP",",","and","Tommi","help","Bearmon",",","Kotemon",",","and","the","Babi","and","In-Train","Digimon","into","reassembl","Ornismon","'s","pictur",".","Is","the","legend","true","?","And","what","are","the","connect","between","D'Arcmon",",","HippoGryphomon",",","and","the","evil","Murmuxmon","?"],"lemmas":["while","travel","on","Ball","the","Trailmon",",","Takuya",",","Koji",",","JP",",","Tommy",",","Zoe",",","Neemon",",","and","Bokomon","end","up","on","the","Wandering","Island","where","the","human-type","Digimon","-lrb-","lead","by","d'arcmon","-rrb-","and","the","beast-type","Digimon","-lrb-","lead","by","hippogryphomon","-rrb-","be","at","war","with","each","other",".","Takuya","and","Co.","befriend","Bearmon","-lrb-","younger","brother","of","grizzlymon","-rrb-","and","Kotemon","-lrb-","younger","brother","of","Dinohyumon","-rrb-","who","be","friend",".","Takuya","side","with","dinohyumon","and","the","human-type","Digimon","and","Koji","side","with","grizzlymon","and","the","beast-type","Digimon",".","when","they","hear","the","legend","that","the","bird","Ornismon","can","end","the","war",",","Zoe",",","JP",",","and","Tommy","help","Bearmon",",","Kotemon",",","and","the","Baby","and","In-Training","Digimon","into","reassemble","Ornismon","'s","picture",".","be","the","legend","true","?","and","what","be","the","connection","between","D'Arcmon",",","HippoGryphomon",",","and","the","evil","Murmuxmon","?"],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["While traveling on","traveling on Ball","on Ball the","Ball the Trailmon","the Trailmon ,","Trailmon , Takuya",", Takuya ,","Takuya , Koji",", Koji ,","Koji , JP",", JP ,","JP , Tommy",", Tommy ,","Tommy , Zoe",", Zoe ,","Zoe , Neemon",", Neemon ,","Neemon , and",", and Bokomon","and Bokomon end","Bokomon end up","end up on","up on the","on the Wandering","the Wandering Island","Wandering Island where","Island where the","where the Human-type","the Human-type Digimon","Human-type Digimon (","Digimon ( led","( led by","led by D'Arcmon","by D'Arcmon )","D'Arcmon ) and",") and the","and the Beast-type","the Beast-type Digimon","Beast-type Digimon (","Digimon ( led","( led by","led by HippoGryphomon","by HippoGryphomon )","HippoGryphomon ) are",") are at","are at war","at war with","war with each","with each other","Takuya and Co.","and Co. befriend","Co. befriend Bearmon","befriend Bearmon (","Bearmon ( younger","( younger brother","younger brother of","brother of Grizzlymon","of Grizzlymon )","Grizzlymon ) and",") and Kotemon","and Kotemon (","Kotemon ( younger","( younger brother","younger brother of","brother of Dinohyumon","of Dinohyumon )","Dinohyumon ) who",") who are","who are friends","Takuya sides with","sides with Dinohyumon","with Dinohyumon and","Dinohyumon and the","and the Human-type","the Human-type Digimon","Human-type Digimon and","Digimon and Koji","and Koji sides","Koji sides with","sides with Grizzlymon","with Grizzlymon and","Grizzlymon and the","and the Beast-type","the Beast-type Digimon","When they hear","they hear the","hear the legend","the legend that","legend that the","that the bird","the bird Ornismon","bird Ornismon can","Ornismon can end","can end the","end the war","the war ,","war , Zoe",", Zoe ,","Zoe , JP",", JP ,","JP , and",", and Tommy","and Tommy help","Tommy help Bearmon","help Bearmon ,","Bearmon , Kotemon",", Kotemon ,","Kotemon , and",", and the","and the Baby","the Baby and","Baby and In-Training","and In-Training Digimon","In-Training Digimon into","Digimon into reassembling","into reassembling Ornismon","reassembling Ornismon 's","Ornismon 's picture","Is the legend","the legend true","And what are","what are the","are the connections","the connections between","connections between D'Arcmon","between D'Arcmon ,","D'Arcmon , HippoGryphomon",", HippoGryphomon ,","HippoGryphomon , and",", and the","and the evil","the evil Murmuxmon"],"2grams":["While traveling","traveling on","on Ball","Ball the","the Trailmon","Trailmon ,",", Takuya","Takuya ,",", Koji","Koji ,",", JP","JP ,",", Tommy","Tommy ,",", Zoe","Zoe ,",", Neemon","Neemon ,",", and","and Bokomon","Bokomon end","end up","up on","on the","the Wandering","Wandering Island","Island where","where the","the Human-type","Human-type Digimon","Digimon (","( led","led by","by D'Arcmon","D'Arcmon )",") and","and the","the Beast-type","Beast-type Digimon","Digimon (","( led","led by","by HippoGryphomon","HippoGryphomon )",") are","are at","at war","war with","with each","each other","Takuya and","and Co.","Co. befriend","befriend Bearmon","Bearmon (","( younger","younger brother","brother of","of Grizzlymon","Grizzlymon )",") and","and Kotemon","Kotemon (","( younger","younger brother","brother of","of Dinohyumon","Dinohyumon )",") who","who are","are friends","Takuya sides","sides with","with Dinohyumon","Dinohyumon and","and the","the Human-type","Human-type Digimon","Digimon and","and Koji","Koji sides","sides with","with Grizzlymon","Grizzlymon and","and the","the Beast-type","Beast-type Digimon","When they","they hear","hear the","the legend","legend that","that the","the bird","bird Ornismon","Ornismon can","can end","end the","the war","war ,",", Zoe","Zoe ,",", JP","JP ,",", and","and Tommy","Tommy help","help Bearmon","Bearmon ,",", Kotemon","Kotemon ,",", and","and the","the Baby","Baby and","and In-Training","In-Training Digimon","Digimon into","into reassembling","reassembling Ornismon","Ornismon 's","'s picture","Is the","the legend","legend true","And what","what are","are the","the connections","connections between","between D'Arcmon","D'Arcmon ,",", HippoGryphomon","HippoGryphomon ,",", and","and the","the evil","evil Murmuxmon"]}