{"title":"I Corrupt All Cops","plot":"Hong Kong under British rule, when corruption and bribery were the order of the day. Chinese Chief Constable Lak (Tony Leung Ka Fai) together with his gang, Uncorn (Anthony Wong), Gale (Eason Chan), Gold (Wong Jing), laundered drug money.","genres":["Crime"," History"],"stems":["Hong","Kong","under","British","rule",",","when","corrupt","and","briberi","were","the","order","of","the","day",".","Chines","Chief","Constabl","Lak","(","Toni","Leung","Ka","Fai",")","togeth","with","his","gang",",","Uncorn","(","Anthoni","Wong",")",",","Gale","(","Eason","Chan",")",",","Gold","(","Wong","Jing",")",",","launder","drug","money","."],"lemmas":["Hong","Kong","under","british","rule",",","when","corruption","and","bribery","be","the","order","of","the","day",".","Chinese","Chief","Constable","Lak","-lrb-","Tony","Leung","ka","fai","-rrb-","together","with","he","gang",",","Uncorn","-lrb-","Anthony","Wong","-rrb-",",","Gale","-lrb-","Eason","Chan","-rrb-",",","Gold","-lrb-","Wong","Jing","-rrb-",",","launder","drug","money","."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Hong Kong under","Kong under British","under British rule","British rule ,","rule , when",", when corruption","when corruption and","corruption and bribery","and bribery were","bribery were the","were the order","the order of","order of the","of the day","Chinese Chief Constable","Chief Constable Lak","Constable Lak (","Lak ( Tony","( Tony Leung","Tony Leung Ka","Leung Ka Fai","Ka Fai )","Fai ) together",") together with","together with his","with his gang","his gang ,","gang , Uncorn",", Uncorn (","Uncorn ( Anthony","( Anthony Wong","Anthony Wong )","Wong ) ,",") , Gale",", Gale (","Gale ( Eason","( Eason Chan","Eason Chan )","Chan ) ,",") , Gold",", Gold (","Gold ( Wong","( Wong Jing","Wong Jing )","Jing ) ,",") , laundered",", laundered drug","laundered drug money"],"2grams":["Hong Kong","Kong under","under British","British rule","rule ,",", when","when corruption","corruption and","and bribery","bribery were","were the","the order","order of","of the","the day","Chinese Chief","Chief Constable","Constable Lak","Lak (","( Tony","Tony Leung","Leung Ka","Ka Fai","Fai )",") together","together with","with his","his gang","gang ,",", Uncorn","Uncorn (","( Anthony","Anthony Wong","Wong )",") ,",", Gale","Gale (","( Eason","Eason Chan","Chan )",") ,",", Gold","Gold (","( Wong","Wong Jing","Jing )",") ,",", laundered","laundered drug","drug money"]}