{"title":"Rakhi Bhijigala Aakhi Luha Re","plot":"Rajesh ( Mihir Das) & Minu lost their parent at their childhood. Rajesh is everything for Minu. Minu falls love with Ajay (Siddhant Mahapatra) . They get married . Ajay's uncle has other thing in mind. He decided to wipe out Minu from Ajay's life.","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["Rajesh","(","Mihir","Das",")","&","Minu","lost","their","parent","at","their","childhood",".","Rajesh","is","everyth","for","Minu",".","Minu","fall","love","with","Ajay","(","Siddhant","Mahapatra",")",".","They","get","marri",".","Ajay","'s","uncl","has","other","thing","in","mind",".","He","decid","to","wipe","out","Minu","from","Ajay","'s","life","."],"lemmas":["Rajesh","-lrb-","Mihir","Das","-rrb-","&","Minu","lose","they","parent","at","they","childhood",".","Rajesh","be","everything","for","Minu",".","Minu","fall","love","with","Ajay","-lrb-","Siddhant","Mahapatra","-rrb-",".","they","get","marry",".","Ajay","'s","uncle","have","other","thing","in","mind",".","he","decide","to","wipe","out","Minu","from","Ajay","'s","life","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","ORGANIZATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Rajesh ( Mihir","( Mihir Das","Mihir Das )","Das ) &",") & Minu","& Minu lost","Minu lost their","lost their parent","their parent at","parent at their","at their childhood","Rajesh is everything","is everything for","everything for Minu","Minu falls love","falls love with","love with Ajay","with Ajay (","Ajay ( Siddhant","( Siddhant Mahapatra","Siddhant Mahapatra )","They get married","Ajay 's uncle","'s uncle has","uncle has other","has other thing","other thing in","thing in mind","He decided to","decided to wipe","to wipe out","wipe out Minu","out Minu from","Minu from Ajay","from Ajay 's","Ajay 's life"],"2grams":["Rajesh (","( Mihir","Mihir Das","Das )",") &","& Minu","Minu lost","lost their","their parent","parent at","at their","their childhood","Rajesh is","is everything","everything for","for Minu","Minu falls","falls love","love with","with Ajay","Ajay (","( Siddhant","Siddhant Mahapatra","Mahapatra )","They get","get married","Ajay 's","'s uncle","uncle has","has other","other thing","thing in","in mind","He decided","decided to","to wipe","wipe out","out Minu","Minu from","from Ajay","Ajay 's","'s life"]}