{"title":"What is Minimalism?: The American Perspective 1958-1968","plot":"A documentary that provides answers, featuring the exhibit, A Minimal Future? Art as Object 1958-1968 at the Museum of Contemporary Art in Los Angeles with the participation of Carl Andre, John Chamberlain, Robert Irwin, Donald Judd, Sol LeWitt, Brice Marden, Robert Morris, Claes Oldenburg, Robert Ryman, Tony Smith and Frank Stella.","genres":["Documentary"],"stems":["A","documentari","that","provid","answer",",","featur","the","exhibit",",","A","Minim","Futur","?","Art","as","Object","1958-1968","at","the","Museum","of","Contemporari","Art","in","Los","Angele","with","the","particip","of","Carl","Andre",",","John","Chamberlain",",","Robert","Irwin",",","Donald","Judd",",","Sol","LeWitt",",","Brice","Marden",",","Robert","Morri",",","Clae","Oldenburg",",","Robert","Ryman",",","Toni","Smith","and","Frank","Stella","."],"lemmas":["a","documentary","that","provide","answer",",","feature","the","exhibit",",","a","minimal","Future","?","art","as","Object","1958-1968","at","the","Museum","of","Contemporary","Art","in","Los","Angeles","with","the","participation","of","Carl","Andre",",","John","Chamberlain",",","Robert","Irwin",",","Donald","Judd",",","Sol","LeWitt",",","Brice","Marden",",","Robert","Morris",",","Claes","Oldenburg",",","Robert","Ryman",",","Tony","Smith","and","Frank","Stella","."],"named_entities":["ORGANIZATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["A documentary that","documentary that provides","that provides answers","provides answers ,","answers , featuring",", featuring the","featuring the exhibit","the exhibit ,","exhibit , A",", A Minimal","A Minimal Future","Art as Object","as Object 1958-1968","Object 1958-1968 at","1958-1968 at the","at the Museum","the Museum of","Museum of Contemporary","of Contemporary Art","Contemporary Art in","Art in Los","in Los Angeles","Los Angeles with","Angeles with the","with the participation","the participation of","participation of Carl","of Carl Andre","Carl Andre ,","Andre , John",", John Chamberlain","John Chamberlain ,","Chamberlain , Robert",", Robert Irwin","Robert Irwin ,","Irwin , Donald",", Donald Judd","Donald Judd ,","Judd , Sol",", Sol LeWitt","Sol LeWitt ,","LeWitt , Brice",", Brice Marden","Brice Marden ,","Marden , Robert",", Robert Morris","Robert Morris ,","Morris , Claes",", Claes Oldenburg","Claes Oldenburg ,","Oldenburg , Robert",", Robert Ryman","Robert Ryman ,","Ryman , Tony",", Tony Smith","Tony Smith and","Smith and Frank","and Frank Stella"],"2grams":["A documentary","documentary that","that provides","provides answers","answers ,",", featuring","featuring the","the exhibit","exhibit ,",", A","A Minimal","Minimal Future","Art as","as Object","Object 1958-1968","1958-1968 at","at the","the Museum","Museum of","of Contemporary","Contemporary Art","Art in","in Los","Los Angeles","Angeles with","with the","the participation","participation of","of Carl","Carl Andre","Andre ,",", John","John Chamberlain","Chamberlain ,",", Robert","Robert Irwin","Irwin ,",", Donald","Donald Judd","Judd ,",", Sol","Sol LeWitt","LeWitt ,",", Brice","Brice Marden","Marden ,",", Robert","Robert Morris","Morris ,",", Claes","Claes Oldenburg","Oldenburg ,",", Robert","Robert Ryman","Ryman ,",", Tony","Tony Smith","Smith and","and Frank","Frank Stella"]}