{"title":"Cosimo and Nicole","plot":"2011. Genoa. G8. Cosimo, an Italian boy, helps Nicole, French. A look: it is love. Then the two boys return to Genoa; here they work for a friend, Paul, concert organizer. This goes on until Alioune, a young illegal immigrant, falls from a scaffold, working for a stage with Cosimo. The boy remains there, abandoned by Paul, Cosmas and Nicole.","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["2011",".","Genoa",".","G8",".","Cosimo",",","an","Italian","boy",",","help","Nicol",",","French",".","A","look",":","it","is","love",".","Then","the","two","boy","return","to","Genoa",";","here","they","work","for","a","friend",",","Paul",",","concert","organ",".","This","goe","on","until","Alioun",",","a","young","illeg","immigr",",","fall","from","a","scaffold",",","work","for","a","stage","with","Cosimo",".","The","boy","remain","there",",","abandon","by","Paul",",","Cosma","and","Nicol","."],"lemmas":["2011",".","Genoa",".","g8",".","Cosimo",",","a","italian","boy",",","help","Nicole",",","French",".","a","look",":","it","be","love",".","then","the","two","boy","return","to","Genoa",";","here","they","work","for","a","friend",",","Paul",",","concert","organizer",".","this","go","on","until","Alioune",",","a","young","illegal","immigrant",",","fall","from","a","scaffold",",","work","for","a","stage","with","Cosimo",".","the","boy","remain","there",",","abandon","by","Paul",",","Cosmas","and","Nicole","."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Cosimo , an",", an Italian","an Italian boy","Italian boy ,","boy , helps",", helps Nicole","helps Nicole ,","Nicole , French","A look :","look : it",": it is","it is love","Then the two","the two boys","two boys return","boys return to","return to Genoa","to Genoa ;","Genoa ; here","; here they","here they work","they work for","work for a","for a friend","a friend ,","friend , Paul",", Paul ,","Paul , concert",", concert organizer","This goes on","goes on until","on until Alioune","until Alioune ,","Alioune , a",", a young","a young illegal","young illegal immigrant","illegal immigrant ,","immigrant , falls",", falls from","falls from a","from a scaffold","a scaffold ,","scaffold , working",", working for","working for a","for a stage","a stage with","stage with Cosimo","The boy remains","boy remains there","remains there ,","there , abandoned",", abandoned by","abandoned by Paul","by Paul ,","Paul , Cosmas",", Cosmas and","Cosmas and Nicole"],"2grams":["Cosimo ,",", an","an Italian","Italian boy","boy ,",", helps","helps Nicole","Nicole ,",", French","A look","look :",": it","it is","is love","Then the","the two","two boys","boys return","return to","to Genoa","Genoa ;","; here","here they","they work","work for","for a","a friend","friend ,",", Paul","Paul ,",", concert","concert organizer","This goes","goes on","on until","until Alioune","Alioune ,",", a","a young","young illegal","illegal immigrant","immigrant ,",", falls","falls from","from a","a scaffold","scaffold ,",", working","working for","for a","a stage","stage with","with Cosimo","The boy","boy remains","remains there","there ,",", abandoned","abandoned by","by Paul","Paul ,",", Cosmas","Cosmas and","and Nicole"]}