{"title":"When Ali Came to Ireland","plot":"When Ali Came to Ireland is the story of how Butty Sugrue, a circus strongman from Killorglin, Co. Kerry, pulled off a massive sporting coup in July 1972 when he arranged a fight in Croke Park between 'The Greatest' Muhammad Ali and ex-con Alvin 'Blue' Lewis. The fight had an amazing impact on the people Ali met and on the great man himself.","genres":["Adventure"," History"," Documentary"],"stems":["When","Ali","Came","to","Ireland","is","the","stori","of","how","Butti","Sugru",",","a","circus","strongman","from","Killorglin",",","Co",".","Kerri",",","pull","off","a","massiv","sport","coup","in","Juli","1972","when","he","arrang","a","fight","in","Croke","Park","between","'","The","Greatest","'","Muhammad","Ali","and","ex-con","Alvin","'","Blue","'","Lewi",".","The","fight","had","an","amaz","impact","on","the","peopl","Ali","met","and","on","the","great","man","himself","."],"lemmas":["when","Ali","Came","to","Ireland","be","the","story","of","how","Butty","Sugrue",",","a","circus","strongman","from","Killorglin",",","Co",".","Kerry",",","pull","off","a","massive","sport","coup","in","July","1972","when","he","arrange","a","fight","in","Croke","Park","between","'","the","Greatest","'","Muhammad","Ali","and","ex-con","Alvin","'","Blue","'","Lewis",".","the","fight","have","a","amazing","impact","on","the","people","Ali","meet","and","on","the","great","man","himself","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["When Ali Came","Ali Came to","Came to Ireland","to Ireland is","Ireland is the","is the story","the story of","story of how","of how Butty","how Butty Sugrue","Butty Sugrue ,","Sugrue , a",", a circus","a circus strongman","circus strongman from","strongman from Killorglin","from Killorglin ,","Killorglin , Co","Kerry , pulled",", pulled off","pulled off a","off a massive","a massive sporting","massive sporting coup","sporting coup in","coup in July","in July 1972","July 1972 when","1972 when he","when he arranged","he arranged a","arranged a fight","a fight in","fight in Croke","in Croke Park","Croke Park between","Park between '","between ' The","' The Greatest","The Greatest '","Greatest ' Muhammad","' Muhammad Ali","Muhammad Ali and","Ali and ex-con","and ex-con Alvin","ex-con Alvin '","Alvin ' Blue","' Blue '","Blue ' Lewis","The fight had","fight had an","had an amazing","an amazing impact","amazing impact on","impact on the","on the people","the people Ali","people Ali met","Ali met and","met and on","and on the","on the great","the great man","great man himself"],"2grams":["When Ali","Ali Came","Came to","to Ireland","Ireland is","is the","the story","story of","of how","how Butty","Butty Sugrue","Sugrue ,",", a","a circus","circus strongman","strongman from","from Killorglin","Killorglin ,",", Co","Kerry ,",", pulled","pulled off","off a","a massive","massive sporting","sporting coup","coup in","in July","July 1972","1972 when","when he","he arranged","arranged a","a fight","fight in","in Croke","Croke Park","Park between","between '","' The","The Greatest","Greatest '","' Muhammad","Muhammad Ali","Ali and","and ex-con","ex-con Alvin","Alvin '","' Blue","Blue '","' Lewis","The fight","fight had","had an","an amazing","amazing impact","impact on","on the","the people","people Ali","Ali met","met and","and on","on the","the great","great man","man himself"]}