{"title":"Perahu kertas 2","plot":"Coming home from Bali, Kugy try to avoid Keenan and Remi, Karel home to calm down (Ben Kasyafani), his brother. Keenan who feel lost even looking Kugy. Through Noni, Keenan knows that the first Kugy abstain from Keenan, as well as Noni and Eko, is because it actually Kugy love Keenan, but hindered by the proximity of Keenan and Wanda (Kimberly Ryder). Kugy Keenan decided to meet to finalize their pent-up feelings. However, event-by-event then interweave, unite and separate hearts, alternating between Kugy, Keenan, Remi, Luhde, and also Siska along with other people around them. Even opening the how the relationship Pak Wayan and Keenan's parents, Lena (Ira Wibowo) and Adri. Paper boat on a river flowing, swinging looking lovely heart .","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["Come","home","from","Bali",",","Kugi","tri","to","avoid","Keenan","and","Remi",",","Karel","home","to","calm","down","(","Ben","Kasyafani",")",",","his","brother",".","Keenan","who","feel","lost","even","look","Kugi",".","Through","Noni",",","Keenan","know","that","the","first","Kugi","abstain","from","Keenan",",","as","well","as","Noni","and","Eko",",","is","becaus","it","actual","Kugi","love","Keenan",",","but","hinder","by","the","proxim","of","Keenan","and","Wanda","(","Kimber","Ryder",")",".","Kugi","Keenan","decid","to","meet","to","final","their","pent-up","feel",".","Howev",",","event-by-ev","then","interweav",",","unit","and","separ","heart",",","altern","between","Kugi",",","Keenan",",","Remi",",","Luhd",",","and","also","Siska","along","with","other","peopl","around","them",".","Even","open","the","how","the","relationship","Pak","Wayan","and","Keenan","'s","parent",",","Lena","(","Ira","Wibowo",")","and","Adri",".","Paper","boat","on","a","river","flow",",","swing","look","love","heart","."],"lemmas":["come","home","from","Bali",",","Kugy","try","to","avoid","Keenan","and","Remi",",","Karel","home","to","calm","down","-lrb-","Ben","Kasyafani","-rrb-",",","he","brother",".","Keenan","who","feel","lose","even","look","Kugy",".","through","Noni",",","Keenan","know","that","the","first","Kugy","abstain","from","Keenan",",","as","well","as","Noni","and","Eko",",","be","because","it","actually","Kugy","love","Keenan",",","but","hinder","by","the","proximity","of","Keenan","and","Wanda","-lrb-","Kimberly","Ryder","-rrb-",".","Kugy","Keenan","decide","to","meet","to","finalize","they","pent-up","feeling",".","however",",","event-by-event","then","interweave",",","unite","and","separate","heart",",","alternate","between","Kugy",",","Keenan",",","Remi",",","Luhde",",","and","also","Siska","along","with","other","people","around","they",".","even","open","the","how","the","relationship","Pak","Wayan","and","Keenan","'s","parent",",","Lena","-lrb-","Ira","Wibowo","-rrb-","and","Adri",".","paper","boat","on","a","river","flow",",","swing","look","lovely","heart","."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Coming home from","home from Bali","from Bali ,","Bali , Kugy",", Kugy try","Kugy try to","try to avoid","to avoid Keenan","avoid Keenan and","Keenan and Remi","and Remi ,","Remi , Karel",", Karel home","Karel home to","home to calm","to calm down","calm down (","down ( Ben","( Ben Kasyafani","Ben Kasyafani )","Kasyafani ) ,",") , his",", his brother","Keenan who feel","who feel lost","feel lost even","lost even looking","even looking Kugy","Through Noni ,","Noni , Keenan",", Keenan knows","Keenan knows that","knows that the","that the first","the first Kugy","first Kugy abstain","Kugy abstain from","abstain from Keenan","from Keenan ,","Keenan , as",", as well","as well as","well as Noni","as Noni and","Noni and Eko","and Eko ,","Eko , is",", is because","is because it","because it actually","it actually Kugy","actually Kugy love","Kugy love Keenan","love Keenan ,","Keenan , but",", but hindered","but hindered by","hindered by the","by the proximity","the proximity of","proximity of Keenan","of Keenan and","Keenan and Wanda","and Wanda (","Wanda ( Kimberly","( Kimberly Ryder","Kimberly Ryder )","Kugy Keenan decided","Keenan decided to","decided to meet","to meet to","meet to finalize","to finalize their","finalize their pent-up","their pent-up feelings","However , event-by-event",", event-by-event then","event-by-event then interweave","then interweave ,","interweave , unite",", unite and","unite and separate","and separate hearts","separate hearts ,","hearts , alternating",", alternating between","alternating between Kugy","between Kugy ,","Kugy , Keenan",", Keenan ,","Keenan , Remi",", Remi ,","Remi , Luhde",", Luhde ,","Luhde , and",", and also","and also Siska","also Siska along","Siska along with","along with other","with other people","other people around","people around them","Even opening the","opening the how","the how the","how the relationship","the relationship Pak","relationship Pak Wayan","Pak Wayan and","Wayan and Keenan","and Keenan 's","Keenan 's parents","'s parents ,","parents , Lena",", Lena (","Lena ( Ira","( Ira Wibowo","Ira Wibowo )","Wibowo ) and",") and Adri","Paper boat on","boat on a","on a river","a river flowing","river flowing ,","flowing , swinging",", swinging looking","swinging looking lovely","looking lovely heart"],"2grams":["Coming home","home from","from Bali","Bali ,",", Kugy","Kugy try","try to","to avoid","avoid Keenan","Keenan and","and Remi","Remi ,",", Karel","Karel home","home to","to calm","calm down","down (","( Ben","Ben Kasyafani","Kasyafani )",") ,",", his","his brother","Keenan who","who feel","feel lost","lost even","even looking","looking Kugy","Through Noni","Noni ,",", Keenan","Keenan knows","knows that","that the","the first","first Kugy","Kugy abstain","abstain from","from Keenan","Keenan ,",", as","as well","well as","as Noni","Noni and","and Eko","Eko ,",", is","is because","because it","it actually","actually Kugy","Kugy love","love Keenan","Keenan ,",", but","but hindered","hindered by","by the","the proximity","proximity of","of Keenan","Keenan and","and Wanda","Wanda (","( Kimberly","Kimberly Ryder","Ryder )","Kugy Keenan","Keenan decided","decided to","to meet","meet to","to finalize","finalize their","their pent-up","pent-up feelings","However ,",", event-by-event","event-by-event then","then interweave","interweave ,",", unite","unite and","and separate","separate hearts","hearts ,",", alternating","alternating between","between Kugy","Kugy ,",", Keenan","Keenan ,",", Remi","Remi ,",", Luhde","Luhde ,",", and","and also","also Siska","Siska along","along with","with other","other people","people around","around them","Even opening","opening the","the how","how the","the relationship","relationship Pak","Pak Wayan","Wayan and","and Keenan","Keenan 's","'s parents","parents ,",", Lena","Lena (","( Ira","Ira Wibowo","Wibowo )",") and","and Adri","Paper boat","boat on","on a","a river","river flowing","flowing ,",", swinging","swinging looking","looking lovely","lovely heart"]}