{"title":"Cars, Trains, Buses and Planes: A Cross-Societal Look at Transportation","plot":"Shawn Verma and Natasha Kumar, two undergraduate students at Brown University, filmed this documentary as part of an independent study course, which was commissioned by Brown University, during their Spring 2012 semester abroad in Washington D.C., USA; Sao Paulo, Brazil; Hanoi, Vietnam; and Bushbuckridge, South Africa.","genres":["Documentary"," Drama"],"stems":["Shawn","Verma","and","Natasha","Kumar",",","two","undergradu","student","at","Brown","Univers",",","film","this","documentari","as","part","of","an","independ","studi","cours",",","which","was","commiss","by","Brown","Univers",",","dure","their","Spring","2012","semest","abroad","in","Washington","D.C.",",","USA",";","Sao","Paulo",",","Brazil",";","Hanoi",",","Vietnam",";","and","Bushbuckridg",",","South","Africa","."],"lemmas":["Shawn","Verma","and","Natasha","Kumar",",","two","undergraduate","student","at","Brown","University",",","film","this","documentary","as","part","of","a","independent","study","course",",","which","be","commission","by","Brown","University",",","during","they","spring","2012","semester","abroad","in","Washington","D.C.",",","USA",";","Sao","Paulo",",","Brazil",";","Hanoi",",","Vietnam",";","and","Bushbuckridge",",","South","Africa","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","ORGANIZATION","ORGANIZATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION"],"3grams":["Shawn Verma and","Verma and Natasha","and Natasha Kumar","Natasha Kumar ,","Kumar , two",", two undergraduate","two undergraduate students","undergraduate students at","students at Brown","at Brown University","Brown University ,","University , filmed",", filmed this","filmed this documentary","this documentary as","documentary as part","as part of","part of an","of an independent","an independent study","independent study course","study course ,","course , which",", which was","which was commissioned","was commissioned by","commissioned by Brown","by Brown University","Brown University ,","University , during",", during their","during their Spring","their Spring 2012","Spring 2012 semester","2012 semester abroad","semester abroad in","abroad in Washington","in Washington D.C.","Washington D.C. ,","D.C. , USA",", USA ;","USA ; Sao","; Sao Paulo","Sao Paulo ,","Paulo , Brazil",", Brazil ;","Brazil ; Hanoi","; Hanoi ,","Hanoi , Vietnam",", Vietnam ;","Vietnam ; and","; and Bushbuckridge","and Bushbuckridge ,","Bushbuckridge , South",", South Africa"],"2grams":["Shawn Verma","Verma and","and Natasha","Natasha Kumar","Kumar ,",", two","two undergraduate","undergraduate students","students at","at Brown","Brown University","University ,",", filmed","filmed this","this documentary","documentary as","as part","part of","of an","an independent","independent study","study course","course ,",", which","which was","was commissioned","commissioned by","by Brown","Brown University","University ,",", during","during their","their Spring","Spring 2012","2012 semester","semester abroad","abroad in","in Washington","Washington D.C.","D.C. ,",", USA","USA ;","; Sao","Sao Paulo","Paulo ,",", Brazil","Brazil ;","; Hanoi","Hanoi ,",", Vietnam","Vietnam ;","; and","and Bushbuckridge","Bushbuckridge ,",", South","South Africa"]}