{"title":"Sobre sete ondas verdes espumantes","plot":"Santiago, Amsterdam, Berlin, Colony, Paris, London, Porto Alegre, São Paulo. Cities that have witnessed the the short life of the poet, playwright and writer Caio Fernando Abreu (1948-1996)...","genres":["Documentary"],"stems":["Santiago",",","Amsterdam",",","Berlin",",","Coloni",",","Pari",",","London",",","Porto","Alegr",",","São","Paulo",".","Citi","that","have","wit","the","the","short","life","of","the","poet",",","playwright","and","writer","Caio","Fernando","Abreu","(","1948-1996",")","..."],"lemmas":["Santiago",",","Amsterdam",",","Berlin",",","Colony",",","Paris",",","London",",","Porto","Alegre",",","São","Paulo",".","city","that","have","witness","the","the","short","life","of","the","poet",",","playwright","and","writer","Caio","Fernando","Abreu","-lrb-","1948-1996","-rrb-","..."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","ORGANIZATION","LOCATION","LOCATION","ORGANIZATION","LOCATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["Santiago , Amsterdam",", Amsterdam ,","Amsterdam , Berlin",", Berlin ,","Berlin , Colony",", Colony ,","Colony , Paris",", Paris ,","Paris , London",", London ,","London , Porto",", Porto Alegre","Porto Alegre ,","Alegre , São",", São Paulo","Cities that have","that have witnessed","have witnessed the","witnessed the the","the the short","the short life","short life of","life of the","of the poet","the poet ,","poet , playwright",", playwright and","playwright and writer","and writer Caio","writer Caio Fernando","Caio Fernando Abreu","Fernando Abreu (","Abreu ( 1948-1996","( 1948-1996 )","1948-1996 ) ..."],"2grams":["Santiago ,",", Amsterdam","Amsterdam ,",", Berlin","Berlin ,",", Colony","Colony ,",", Paris","Paris ,",", London","London ,",", Porto","Porto Alegre","Alegre ,",", São","São Paulo","Cities that","that have","have witnessed","witnessed the","the the","the short","short life","life of","of the","the poet","poet ,",", playwright","playwright and","and writer","writer Caio","Caio Fernando","Fernando Abreu","Abreu (","( 1948-1996","1948-1996 )",") ..."]}