{"title":"Fan Film Saga Part 1: Icons of Horror","plot":"Director Russell, head of a secret government agency, is in search of the Necronomicon and makes a deal with Freddy Krueger to find the book and release it's powers by spilling the blood of Ash Williams. Freddy recruits Michael Myers and Jason Voorhees as they battle Ghostface and Leatherface on their way to finding Ash Williams. AKA. Freddy vs Jason vs Myers vs Leatherface vs Ghostface vs Ash Williams","genres":["Horror"],"stems":["Director","Russel",",","head","of","a","secret","govern","agenc",",","is","in","search","of","the","Necronomicon","and","make","a","deal","with","Freddi","Krueger","to","find","the","book","and","releas","it","'s","power","by","spill","the","blood","of","Ash","William",".","Freddi","recruit","Michael","Myer","and","Jason","Voorhe","as","they","battl","Ghostfac","and","Leatherfac","on","their","way","to","find","Ash","William",".","AKA",".","Freddi","vs","Jason","vs","Myer","vs","Leatherfac","vs","Ghostfac","vs","Ash","William"],"lemmas":["Director","Russell",",","head","of","a","secret","government","agency",",","be","in","search","of","the","Necronomicon","and","make","a","deal","with","Freddy","Krueger","to","find","the","book","and","release","it","'s","power","by","spilling","the","blood","of","Ash","Williams",".","Freddy","recruit","Michael","Myers","and","Jason","Voorhees","as","they","battle","Ghostface","and","Leatherface","on","they","way","to","find","Ash","Williams",".","aka",".","Freddy","vs","Jason","vs","Myers","vs","Leatherface","vs","Ghostface","vs","Ash","Williams"],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION"],"3grams":["Director Russell ,","Russell , head",", head of","head of a","of a secret","a secret government","secret government agency","government agency ,","agency , is",", is in","is in search","in search of","search of the","of the Necronomicon","the Necronomicon and","Necronomicon and makes","and makes a","makes a deal","a deal with","deal with Freddy","with Freddy Krueger","Freddy Krueger to","Krueger to find","to find the","find the book","the book and","book and release","and release it","release it 's","it 's powers","'s powers by","powers by spilling","by spilling the","spilling the blood","the blood of","blood of Ash","of Ash Williams","Freddy recruits Michael","recruits Michael Myers","Michael Myers and","Myers and Jason","and Jason Voorhees","Jason Voorhees as","Voorhees as they","as they battle","they battle Ghostface","battle Ghostface and","Ghostface and Leatherface","and Leatherface on","Leatherface on their","on their way","their way to","way to finding","to finding Ash","finding Ash Williams","Freddy vs Jason","vs Jason vs","Jason vs Myers","vs Myers vs","Myers vs Leatherface","vs Leatherface vs","Leatherface vs Ghostface","vs Ghostface vs","Ghostface vs Ash","vs Ash Williams"],"2grams":["Director Russell","Russell ,",", head","head of","of a","a secret","secret government","government agency","agency ,",", is","is in","in search","search of","of the","the Necronomicon","Necronomicon and","and makes","makes a","a deal","deal with","with Freddy","Freddy Krueger","Krueger to","to find","find the","the book","book and","and release","release it","it 's","'s powers","powers by","by spilling","spilling the","the blood","blood of","of Ash","Ash Williams","Freddy recruits","recruits Michael","Michael Myers","Myers and","and Jason","Jason Voorhees","Voorhees as","as they","they battle","battle Ghostface","Ghostface and","and Leatherface","Leatherface on","on their","their way","way to","to finding","finding Ash","Ash Williams","Freddy vs","vs Jason","Jason vs","vs Myers","Myers vs","vs Leatherface","Leatherface vs","vs Ghostface","Ghostface vs","vs Ash","Ash Williams"]}