{"title":"Mon papa est un gangster","plot":"A Montreal gangster is tired of the game, he tries to leave. But before taking his retirement, he has to accomplish one last job. His wife Sarah (Karine Turcot) and kid Dom (Jeremy Delisle) need him, but life will choose an other path for Emilio (Rami EL Batnigi). A few years later, Dom (Maxim Boulay) and his best friend Matias (Dave Croussette) decide to follow the same path as Emilio.","genres":["Action"],"stems":["A","Montreal","gangster","is","tire","of","the","game",",","he","tri","to","leav",".","But","befor","take","his","retir",",","he","has","to","accomplish","one","last","job",".","His","wife","Sarah","(","Karin","Turcot",")","and","kid","Dom","(","Jeremi","Delisl",")","need","him",",","but","life","will","choos","an","other","path","for","Emilio","(","Rami","EL","Batnigi",")",".","A","few","year","later",",","Dom","(","Maxim","Boulay",")","and","his","best","friend","Matia","(","Dave","Croussett",")","decid","to","follow","the","same","path","as","Emilio","."],"lemmas":["a","Montreal","gangster","be","tire","of","the","game",",","he","try","to","leave",".","but","before","take","he","retirement",",","he","have","to","accomplish","one","last","job",".","he","wife","Sarah","-lrb-","Karine","Turcot","-rrb-","and","kid","Dom","-lrb-","Jeremy","Delisle","-rrb-","need","he",",","but","life","will","choose","a","other","path","for","Emilio","-lrb-","Rami","EL","Batnigi","-rrb-",".","a","few","year","later",",","Dom","-lrb-","Maxim","Boulay","-rrb-","and","he","best","friend","Matias","-lrb-","Dave","Croussette","-rrb-","decide","to","follow","the","same","path","as","Emilio","."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["A Montreal gangster","Montreal gangster is","gangster is tired","is tired of","tired of the","of the game","the game ,","game , he",", he tries","he tries to","tries to leave","But before taking","before taking his","taking his retirement","his retirement ,","retirement , he",", he has","he has to","has to accomplish","to accomplish one","accomplish one last","one last job","His wife Sarah","wife Sarah (","Sarah ( Karine","( Karine Turcot","Karine Turcot )","Turcot ) and",") and kid","and kid Dom","kid Dom (","Dom ( Jeremy","( Jeremy Delisle","Jeremy Delisle )","Delisle ) need",") need him","need him ,","him , but",", but life","but life will","life will choose","will choose an","choose an other","an other path","other path for","path for Emilio","for Emilio (","Emilio ( Rami","( Rami EL","Rami EL Batnigi","EL Batnigi )","A few years","few years later","years later ,","later , Dom",", Dom (","Dom ( Maxim","( Maxim Boulay","Maxim Boulay )","Boulay ) and",") and his","and his best","his best friend","best friend Matias","friend Matias (","Matias ( Dave","( Dave Croussette","Dave Croussette )","Croussette ) decide",") decide to","decide to follow","to follow the","follow the same","the same path","same path as","path as Emilio"],"2grams":["A Montreal","Montreal gangster","gangster is","is tired","tired of","of the","the game","game ,",", he","he tries","tries to","to leave","But before","before taking","taking his","his retirement","retirement ,",", he","he has","has to","to accomplish","accomplish one","one last","last job","His wife","wife Sarah","Sarah (","( Karine","Karine Turcot","Turcot )",") and","and kid","kid Dom","Dom (","( Jeremy","Jeremy Delisle","Delisle )",") need","need him","him ,",", but","but life","life will","will choose","choose an","an other","other path","path for","for Emilio","Emilio (","( Rami","Rami EL","EL Batnigi","Batnigi )","A few","few years","years later","later ,",", Dom","Dom (","( Maxim","Maxim Boulay","Boulay )",") and","and his","his best","best friend","friend Matias","Matias (","( Dave","Dave Croussette","Croussette )",") decide","decide to","to follow","follow the","the same","same path","path as","as Emilio"]}