{"title":"Rose","plot":"Ajay (Ajay rao) and Ammu (Shravya) are lovers and though Ajay is good, his group of friends is drunkards. Trouble comes when Ajay is arrested by the police for the murder of Rohan (Tilak) ...","genres":["Drama"," Romance"],"stems":["Ajay","(","Ajay","rao",")","and","Ammu","(","Shravya",")","are","lover","and","though","Ajay","is","good",",","his","group","of","friend","is","drunkard",".","Troubl","come","when","Ajay","is","arrest","by","the","polic","for","the","murder","of","Rohan","(","Tilak",")","..."],"lemmas":["Ajay","-lrb-","Ajay","rao","-rrb-","and","Ammu","-lrb-","Shravya","-rrb-","be","lover","and","though","Ajay","be","good",",","he","group","of","friend","be","drunkard",".","trouble","come","when","Ajay","be","arrest","by","the","police","for","the","murder","of","Rohan","-lrb-","Tilak","-rrb-","..."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Ajay ( Ajay","( Ajay rao","Ajay rao )","rao ) and",") and Ammu","and Ammu (","Ammu ( Shravya","( Shravya )","Shravya ) are",") are lovers","are lovers and","lovers and though","and though Ajay","though Ajay is","Ajay is good","is good ,","good , his",", his group","his group of","group of friends","of friends is","friends is drunkards","Trouble comes when","comes when Ajay","when Ajay is","Ajay is arrested","is arrested by","arrested by the","by the police","the police for","police for the","for the murder","the murder of","murder of Rohan","of Rohan (","Rohan ( Tilak","( Tilak )","Tilak ) ..."],"2grams":["Ajay (","( Ajay","Ajay rao","rao )",") and","and Ammu","Ammu (","( Shravya","Shravya )",") are","are lovers","lovers and","and though","though Ajay","Ajay is","is good","good ,",", his","his group","group of","of friends","friends is","is drunkards","Trouble comes","comes when","when Ajay","Ajay is","is arrested","arrested by","by the","the police","police for","for the","the murder","murder of","of Rohan","Rohan (","( Tilak","Tilak )",") ..."]}