{"title":"Hep Yek","plot":"Cevat decides to kidnap Camilla. Ziya assumes kidnapping operations for Cevat. Ziya elect Sahin for bringing Camilla to Cevat in a package. Sahin brings package from Izmir to Istanbul and his path intersect with to stupids named Altan and Gurkan.","genres":["Comedy"],"stems":["Cevat","decid","to","kidnap","Camilla",".","Ziya","assum","kidnap","oper","for","Cevat",".","Ziya","elect","Sahin","for","bring","Camilla","to","Cevat","in","a","packag",".","Sahin","bring","packag","from","Izmir","to","Istanbul","and","his","path","intersect","with","to","stupid","name","Altan","and","Gurkan","."],"lemmas":["Cevat","decide","to","kidnap","Camilla",".","Ziya","assume","kidnapping","operation","for","Cevat",".","Ziya","elect","Sahin","for","bring","Camilla","to","Cevat","in","a","package",".","Sahin","bring","package","from","Izmir","to","Istanbul","and","he","path","intersect","with","to","stupid","name","Altan","and","Gurkan","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Cevat decides to","decides to kidnap","to kidnap Camilla","Ziya assumes kidnapping","assumes kidnapping operations","kidnapping operations for","operations for Cevat","Ziya elect Sahin","elect Sahin for","Sahin for bringing","for bringing Camilla","bringing Camilla to","Camilla to Cevat","to Cevat in","Cevat in a","in a package","Sahin brings package","brings package from","package from Izmir","from Izmir to","Izmir to Istanbul","to Istanbul and","Istanbul and his","and his path","his path intersect","path intersect with","intersect with to","with to stupids","to stupids named","stupids named Altan","named Altan and","Altan and Gurkan"],"2grams":["Cevat decides","decides to","to kidnap","kidnap Camilla","Ziya assumes","assumes kidnapping","kidnapping operations","operations for","for Cevat","Ziya elect","elect Sahin","Sahin for","for bringing","bringing Camilla","Camilla to","to Cevat","Cevat in","in a","a package","Sahin brings","brings package","package from","from Izmir","Izmir to","to Istanbul","Istanbul and","and his","his path","path intersect","intersect with","with to","to stupids","stupids named","named Altan","Altan and","and Gurkan"]}