{"title":"Jibon Moroner Sathi","plot":"Rivalry exists between Chowdhury and Khan families over years. Abir, adopted son of Ashraf Chowdhury family meets with Kajol, daughter of Aftab Khan in their ways to come home. Abir falls in love of Kajol and search for her after arriving home. Don, brother of local MP Shamser Talukdar, also likes Kajol. Shamser goes with marriage proposal to Khan but he refused and so Shamser threatens to take away her daughter. Khan has to surrender for a case and he wants Chowdhury to keep her daughter safe. Chowdhury accepts Kajol gladly and by the time span she becomes a part of that family and also falls in love with Abir. But the conflict arise as Abir is the adopted child of Aftab Chowdhury.","genres":["Comedy"," Romance"," Drama"],"stems":["Rivalri","exist","between","Chowdhuri","and","Khan","famili","over","year",".","Abir",",","adopt","son","of","Ashraf","Chowdhuri","famili","meet","with","Kajol",",","daughter","of","Aftab","Khan","in","their","way","to","come","home",".","Abir","fall","in","love","of","Kajol","and","search","for","her","after","arriv","home",".","Don",",","brother","of","local","MP","Shamser","Talukdar",",","also","like","Kajol",".","Shamser","goe","with","marriag","propos","to","Khan","but","he","refus","and","so","Shamser","threaten","to","take","away","her","daughter",".","Khan","has","to","surrend","for","a","case","and","he","want","Chowdhuri","to","keep","her","daughter","safe",".","Chowdhuri","accept","Kajol","glad","and","by","the","time","span","she","becom","a","part","of","that","famili","and","also","fall","in","love","with","Abir",".","But","the","conflict","aris","as","Abir","is","the","adopt","child","of","Aftab","Chowdhuri","."],"lemmas":["rivalry","exist","between","Chowdhury","and","Khan","family","over","year",".","Abir",",","adopt","son","of","Ashraf","Chowdhury","family","meet","with","kajol",",","daughter","of","Aftab","Khan","in","they","way","to","come","home",".","Abir","fall","in","love","of","kajol","and","search","for","she","after","arrive","home",".","Don",",","brother","of","local","MP","Shamser","Talukdar",",","also","like","Kajol",".","Shamser","go","with","marriage","proposal","to","Khan","but","he","refuse","and","so","Shamser","threaten","to","take","away","she","daughter",".","Khan","have","to","surrender","for","a","case","and","he","want","Chowdhury","to","keep","she","daughter","safe",".","Chowdhury","accept","Kajol","gladly","and","by","the","time","span","she","become","a","part","of","that","family","and","also","fall","in","love","with","Abir",".","but","the","conflict","arise","as","Abir","be","the","adopted","child","of","Aftab","Chowdhury","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Rivalry exists between","exists between Chowdhury","between Chowdhury and","Chowdhury and Khan","and Khan families","Khan families over","families over years","Abir , adopted",", adopted son","adopted son of","son of Ashraf","of Ashraf Chowdhury","Ashraf Chowdhury family","Chowdhury family meets","family meets with","meets with Kajol","with Kajol ,","Kajol , daughter",", daughter of","daughter of Aftab","of Aftab Khan","Aftab Khan in","Khan in their","in their ways","their ways to","ways to come","to come home","Abir falls in","falls in love","in love of","love of Kajol","of Kajol and","Kajol and search","and search for","search for her","for her after","her after arriving","after arriving home","Don , brother",", brother of","brother of local","of local MP","local MP Shamser","MP Shamser Talukdar","Shamser Talukdar ,","Talukdar , also",", also likes","also likes Kajol","Shamser goes with","goes with marriage","with marriage proposal","marriage proposal to","proposal to Khan","to Khan but","Khan but he","but he refused","he refused and","refused and so","and so Shamser","so Shamser threatens","Shamser threatens to","threatens to take","to take away","take away her","away her daughter","Khan has to","has to surrender","to surrender for","surrender for a","for a case","a case and","case and he","and he wants","he wants Chowdhury","wants Chowdhury to","Chowdhury to keep","to keep her","keep her daughter","her daughter safe","Chowdhury accepts Kajol","accepts Kajol gladly","Kajol gladly and","gladly and by","and by the","by the time","the time span","time span she","span she becomes","she becomes a","becomes a part","a part of","part of that","of that family","that family and","family and also","and also falls","also falls in","falls in love","in love with","love with Abir","But the conflict","the conflict arise","conflict arise as","arise as Abir","as Abir is","Abir is the","is the adopted","the adopted child","adopted child of","child of Aftab","of Aftab Chowdhury"],"2grams":["Rivalry exists","exists between","between Chowdhury","Chowdhury and","and Khan","Khan families","families over","over years","Abir ,",", adopted","adopted son","son of","of Ashraf","Ashraf Chowdhury","Chowdhury family","family meets","meets with","with Kajol","Kajol ,",", daughter","daughter of","of Aftab","Aftab Khan","Khan in","in their","their ways","ways to","to come","come home","Abir falls","falls in","in love","love of","of Kajol","Kajol and","and search","search for","for her","her after","after arriving","arriving home","Don ,",", brother","brother of","of local","local MP","MP Shamser","Shamser Talukdar","Talukdar ,",", also","also likes","likes Kajol","Shamser goes","goes with","with marriage","marriage proposal","proposal to","to Khan","Khan but","but he","he refused","refused and","and so","so Shamser","Shamser threatens","threatens to","to take","take away","away her","her daughter","Khan has","has to","to surrender","surrender for","for a","a case","case and","and he","he wants","wants Chowdhury","Chowdhury to","to keep","keep her","her daughter","daughter safe","Chowdhury accepts","accepts Kajol","Kajol gladly","gladly and","and by","by the","the time","time span","span she","she becomes","becomes a","a part","part of","of that","that family","family and","and also","also falls","falls in","in love","love with","with Abir","But the","the conflict","conflict arise","arise as","as Abir","Abir is","is the","the adopted","adopted child","child of","of Aftab","Aftab Chowdhury"]}