{"title":"Chhakka Panja","plot":"Story of five friends Raja (Deepak Raj Giri), Saraswoti (Jeetu Nepal), Magne (Kedar Ghimire) and Buddhi (Buddhi Tamang). Raja is rich but illiterate and enjoys life, and tells his friends to not get married or hold any job. However, he secretly has affairs with married women.Then one day Raja gets married to Champa (Priyanka Karki), and the story enters a serious mode.","genres":["Comedy"," Family"," Drama"],"stems":["Stori","of","five","friend","Raja","(","Deepak","Raj","Giri",")",",","Saraswoti","(","Jeetu","Nepal",")",",","Magn","(","Kedar","Ghimir",")","and","Buddhi","(","Buddhi","Tamang",")",".","Raja","is","rich","but","illiter","and","enjoy","life",",","and","tell","his","friend","to","not","get","marri","or","hold","ani","job",".","Howev",",","he","secret","has","affair","with","marri","women.Then","one","day","Raja","get","marri","to","Champa","(","Priyanka","Karki",")",",","and","the","stori","enter","a","serious","mode","."],"lemmas":["Story","of","five","friend","Raja","-lrb-","Deepak","Raj","Giri","-rrb-",",","Saraswoti","-lrb-","Jeetu","Nepal","-rrb-",",","Magne","-lrb-","Kedar","Ghimire","-rrb-","and","Buddhi","-lrb-","Buddhi","Tamang","-rrb-",".","Raja","be","rich","but","illiterate","and","enjoy","life",",","and","tell","he","friend","to","not","get","marry","or","hold","any","job",".","however",",","he","secretly","have","affair","with","married","women.then","one","day","Raja","get","marry","to","Champa","-lrb-","Priyanka","Karki","-rrb-",",","and","the","story","enter","a","serious","mode","."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Story of five","of five friends","five friends Raja","friends Raja (","Raja ( Deepak","( Deepak Raj","Deepak Raj Giri","Raj Giri )","Giri ) ,",") , Saraswoti",", Saraswoti (","Saraswoti ( Jeetu","( Jeetu Nepal","Jeetu Nepal )","Nepal ) ,",") , Magne",", Magne (","Magne ( Kedar","( Kedar Ghimire","Kedar Ghimire )","Ghimire ) and",") and Buddhi","and Buddhi (","Buddhi ( Buddhi","( Buddhi Tamang","Buddhi Tamang )","Raja is rich","is rich but","rich but illiterate","but illiterate and","illiterate and enjoys","and enjoys life","enjoys life ,","life , and",", and tells","and tells his","tells his friends","his friends to","friends to not","to not get","not get married","get married or","married or hold","or hold any","hold any job","However , he",", he secretly","he secretly has","secretly has affairs","has affairs with","affairs with married","with married women.Then","married women.Then one","women.Then one day","one day Raja","day Raja gets","Raja gets married","gets married to","married to Champa","to Champa (","Champa ( Priyanka","( Priyanka Karki","Priyanka Karki )","Karki ) ,",") , and",", and the","and the story","the story enters","story enters a","enters a serious","a serious mode"],"2grams":["Story of","of five","five friends","friends Raja","Raja (","( Deepak","Deepak Raj","Raj Giri","Giri )",") ,",", Saraswoti","Saraswoti (","( Jeetu","Jeetu Nepal","Nepal )",") ,",", Magne","Magne (","( Kedar","Kedar Ghimire","Ghimire )",") and","and Buddhi","Buddhi (","( Buddhi","Buddhi Tamang","Tamang )","Raja is","is rich","rich but","but illiterate","illiterate and","and enjoys","enjoys life","life ,",", and","and tells","tells his","his friends","friends to","to not","not get","get married","married or","or hold","hold any","any job","However ,",", he","he secretly","secretly has","has affairs","affairs with","with married","married women.Then","women.Then one","one day","day Raja","Raja gets","gets married","married to","to Champa","Champa (","( Priyanka","Priyanka Karki","Karki )",") ,",", and","and the","the story","story enters","enters a","a serious","serious mode"]}