{"title":"Mi Hermano","plot":"Alexey was born in Russia and adopted by Gabriela, an unmarried woman. Later, Gabriela and Alexey adopted Mateo, another child from Siberia. Over the course of nine years, Alexey and Mateo ...","genres":["Documentary"],"stems":["Alexey","was","born","in","Russia","and","adopt","by","Gabriela",",","an","unmarri","woman",".","Later",",","Gabriela","and","Alexey","adopt","Mateo",",","anoth","child","from","Siberia",".","Over","the","cours","of","nine","year",",","Alexey","and","Mateo","..."],"lemmas":["Alexey","be","bear","in","Russia","and","adopt","by","Gabriela",",","a","unmarried","woman",".","later",",","Gabriela","and","Alexey","adopt","Mateo",",","another","child","from","Siberia",".","over","the","course","of","nine","year",",","Alexey","and","Mateo","..."],"named_entities":["PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON"],"3grams":["Alexey was born","was born in","born in Russia","in Russia and","Russia and adopted","and adopted by","adopted by Gabriela","by Gabriela ,","Gabriela , an",", an unmarried","an unmarried woman","Later , Gabriela",", Gabriela and","Gabriela and Alexey","and Alexey adopted","Alexey adopted Mateo","adopted Mateo ,","Mateo , another",", another child","another child from","child from Siberia","Over the course","the course of","course of nine","of nine years","nine years ,","years , Alexey",", Alexey and","Alexey and Mateo","and Mateo ..."],"2grams":["Alexey was","was born","born in","in Russia","Russia and","and adopted","adopted by","by Gabriela","Gabriela ,",", an","an unmarried","unmarried woman","Later ,",", Gabriela","Gabriela and","and Alexey","Alexey adopted","adopted Mateo","Mateo ,",", another","another child","child from","from Siberia","Over the","the course","course of","of nine","nine years","years ,",", Alexey","Alexey and","and Mateo","Mateo ..."]}