{"title":"L Storm","plot":"Independent Commission Against Corruption (Hong Kong) (ICAC) investigator William Luk (Louis Koo) and Joint Financial Intelligence Unit {JFIU) officer Lau Po-keung (Julian Cheung) are ...","genres":["Action"],"stems":["Independ","Commiss","Against","Corrupt","(","Hong","Kong",")","(","ICAC",")","investig","William","Luk","(","Loui","Koo",")","and","Joint","Financi","Intellig","Unit","{","JFIU",")","offic","Lau","Po-keung","(","Julian","Cheung",")","are","..."],"lemmas":["Independent","Commission","against","Corruption","-lrb-","Hong","Kong","-rrb-","-lrb-","icac","-rrb-","investigator","William","Luk","-lrb-","Louis","Koo","-rrb-","and","Joint","Financial","Intelligence","Unit","-lcb-","JFIU","-rrb-","officer","Lau","Po-keung","-lrb-","Julian","Cheung","-rrb-","be","..."],"named_entities":["ORGANIZATION","LOCATION","ORGANIZATION","PERSON","PERSON","ORGANIZATION","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Independent Commission Against","Commission Against Corruption","Against Corruption (","Corruption ( Hong","( Hong Kong","Hong Kong )","Kong ) (",") ( ICAC","( ICAC )","ICAC ) investigator",") investigator William","investigator William Luk","William Luk (","Luk ( Louis","( Louis Koo","Louis Koo )","Koo ) and",") and Joint","and Joint Financial","Joint Financial Intelligence","Financial Intelligence Unit","Intelligence Unit {","Unit { JFIU","{ JFIU )","JFIU ) officer",") officer Lau","officer Lau Po-keung","Lau Po-keung (","Po-keung ( Julian","( Julian Cheung","Julian Cheung )","Cheung ) are",") are ..."],"2grams":["Independent Commission","Commission Against","Against Corruption","Corruption (","( Hong","Hong Kong","Kong )",") (","( ICAC","ICAC )",") investigator","investigator William","William Luk","Luk (","( Louis","Louis Koo","Koo )",") and","and Joint","Joint Financial","Financial Intelligence","Intelligence Unit","Unit {","{ JFIU","JFIU )",") officer","officer Lau","Lau Po-keung","Po-keung (","( Julian","Julian Cheung","Cheung )",") are","are ..."]}