{"title":"Garabandal, solo Dios lo sabe","plot":"June 18, 1961. In a small village in Northern Spain, San Sebastián de Garabandal, four girls, Conchita, Jacinta, Mari Loli, and Mari Cruz, claim that St. Michael and the Virgin Mary have ...","genres":["Drama"],"stems":["June","18",",","1961",".","In","a","small","villag","in","Northern","Spain",",","San","Sebastián","de","Garaband",",","four","girl",",","Conchita",",","Jacinta",",","Mari","Loli",",","and","Mari","Cruz",",","claim","that","St.","Michael","and","the","Virgin","Mari","have","..."],"lemmas":["June","18",",","1961",".","in","a","small","village","in","Northern","Spain",",","San","Sebastián","de","Garabandal",",","four","girl",",","Conchita",",","Jacinta",",","Mari","Loli",",","and","Mari","Cruz",",","claim","that","St.","Michael","and","the","Virgin","Mary","have","..."],"named_entities":["LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","ORGANIZATION"],"3grams":["June 18 ,","18 , 1961","In a small","a small village","small village in","village in Northern","in Northern Spain","Northern Spain ,","Spain , San",", San Sebastián","San Sebastián de","Sebastián de Garabandal","de Garabandal ,","Garabandal , four",", four girls","four girls ,","girls , Conchita",", Conchita ,","Conchita , Jacinta",", Jacinta ,","Jacinta , Mari",", Mari Loli","Mari Loli ,","Loli , and",", and Mari","and Mari Cruz","Mari Cruz ,","Cruz , claim",", claim that","claim that St.","that St. Michael","St. Michael and","Michael and the","and the Virgin","the Virgin Mary","Virgin Mary have","Mary have ..."],"2grams":["June 18","18 ,",", 1961","In a","a small","small village","village in","in Northern","Northern Spain","Spain ,",", San","San Sebastián","Sebastián de","de Garabandal","Garabandal ,",", four","four girls","girls ,",", Conchita","Conchita ,",", Jacinta","Jacinta ,",", Mari","Mari Loli","Loli ,",", and","and Mari","Mari Cruz","Cruz ,",", claim","claim that","that St.","St. Michael","Michael and","and the","the Virgin","Virgin Mary","Mary have","have ..."]}