{"title":"N.Y. Maxman","plot":"Masayoshi, a first Maxman, is working in New York City in USA. He and Hiro, the grandson of the Maxman author meet and return to Japan. They meet the second Maxman. Elsewhere, Kaho's father...","genres":["Action"],"stems":["Masayoshi",",","a","first","Maxman",",","is","work","in","New","York","Citi","in","USA",".","He","and","Hiro",",","the","grandson","of","the","Maxman","author","meet","and","return","to","Japan",".","They","meet","the","second","Maxman",".","Elsewher",",","Kaho","'s","father","..."],"lemmas":["Masayoshi",",","a","first","Maxman",",","be","work","in","New","York","City","in","USA",".","he","and","Hiro",",","the","grandson","of","the","Maxman","author","meet","and","return","to","Japan",".","they","meet","the","second","Maxman",".","elsewhere",",","Kaho","'s","father","..."],"named_entities":["PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON","LOCATION","PERSON","PERSON"],"3grams":["Masayoshi , a",", a first","a first Maxman","first Maxman ,","Maxman , is",", is working","is working in","working in New","in New York","New York City","York City in","City in USA","He and Hiro","and Hiro ,","Hiro , the",", the grandson","the grandson of","grandson of the","of the Maxman","the Maxman author","Maxman author meet","author meet and","meet and return","and return to","return to Japan","They meet the","meet the second","the second Maxman","Elsewhere , Kaho",", Kaho 's","Kaho 's father","'s father ..."],"2grams":["Masayoshi ,",", a","a first","first Maxman","Maxman ,",", is","is working","working in","in New","New York","York City","City in","in USA","He and","and Hiro","Hiro ,",", the","the grandson","grandson of","of the","the Maxman","Maxman author","author meet","meet and","and return","return to","to Japan","They meet","meet the","the second","second Maxman","Elsewhere ,",", Kaho","Kaho 's","'s father","father ..."]}